so before we get into some of the material today on loss function
그래서 우리는 손실 함수에 재료의 일부에 오늘 도착하기 전에
optimization I wanted to go over some administrative things first
최적화 내가 먼저 일부 관리 일을 통해 가고 싶어
just as a reminder of the person Simon is due on next Wednesday so you have
당신은 그래서 그냥 사람의 신호로 시몬은 다음 주 수요일에 기인한다
roughly nine days left and just as a warning Monday is holidays so there will
약 구일 왼쪽 단지 경고로 월요일이 것 때문에 휴일입니다
be no class in office hours so plan out your time accordingly to make sure that
근무 시간에 더 클래스는, 그래서 확인하기 위해 따라 시간을 계획하지
you can complete the assignment in time of course he also have some late two
당신은 그가 또한 일부 늦게이이 과정의 시간에 과제를 완료 할 수 있습니다
days that you can use and allocate among your silence as you see fit
당신이 사용하고 맞는 볼로 침묵 사이에서 할당 할 수있는 일
ok so I diving into the material first i'd like to remind you where we are
확인을 재료로 그래서 다이빙 먼저 나는 우리가 어디 당신을 생각 나게하고 싶습니다
currently last time we looked at this problem visual recognition as
현재 마지막으로 우리는이 문제를 시각적 인식으로 바라 보았다
specifically at image classification and we're talking about the fact that this
특히 이미지 분류에서 우리는이 사실에 대해 얘기
is actually a very difficult problem right so he just consider the cross
그는 단지 십자가를 고려 바로 때문에 매우 어려운 문제가 실​​제로
product called the possible variations that we have to be robust to when we
제품은 우리가 때를에 강력한해야 가능한 변화라고
recognize any of these categories such as cat just seems like such an
고양이 그냥 그런 것 같아 같은 이러한 범주 중 하나를 인식
intractable and possible problem and not only do we know how to solve these
다루기 힘든 가능한 문제가 아니라 단지 우리가 이것들을 해결하는 방법을 알고
problems now but we can solve this problem for thousands of categories and
문제는 지금 그러나 우리는 종류의 수천을 위해이 문제를 해결할 수 있으며,
the state of the art methods work almost at human accuracy or even slightly
당해 방법의 상태는 거의 인간의 정밀도 혹은 약간 작동
surpassing it and some of those classes and it's also runs nearly in real kind
그것은 그 클래스의 일부를 돌파하고 또한 리얼 종류 거의 실행있어
of your phone and so basically and all of this also happened in the last three
휴대 전화 등 기본적으로이 모든의 또한 마지막 세에서 일어난
years and also you'll be experts by the end of the class on all of this
이 모든에 클래스의 말에 세 또한 수 있습니다 전문가
technology so it's really cool and exciting oK so that's the problem of
기술 그 문제 그래서 정말 시원하고 확인을 흥분 때문에
classification of a commission we talked specifically about the data German
위원회의 분류 우리는 데이터 독일어에 대해 구체적으로 이야기
approaching the fact that we can't just explicitly hardcode these classifiers so
우리가 명시 적으로 이러한 분류를 하드 수 없다는 사실에 접근
we have to actually trained them from Dana and so we looked at the idea of
우리는 실제로 다나에서 그들을 훈련을해야하고 그래서 우리의 생각 보았다
having different the training data having the validation splits where we
다른 갖는 유효성을 갖는 훈련 데이터는 어디 분할 우리
just had our hyper parameters and a test that that you don't touch too much we
우리의 하이퍼 매개 변수와 너무 많이 만지지 않도록하는 테스트를했다 우리
look specifically at the example of the nearest neighbor classifier and someone
가장 가까운 이웃 분류 누군가의 예에서 구체적으로 보면
and the canyons neighbor classifier and I talked about the secret India said
그리고 협곡 이웃 분류와 나는 비밀 인도에 대해 이야기했다
which is our Toyota said that we play with during this class then I introduced
이는 우리의 도요타는 우리가 내가 소개 한 후이 수업 시간에 재생했다
the idea of this approach that I termed paratroop approach which is really that
정말로, 즉 I가 공수 방식 불리는이 방법의 아이디어
we're writing a function from image directly to the tennis courts that have
우리는 바로이 테니스 코트에 이미지에서 함수를 작성하는
10 closest and the spermatic formerly seem to be a long year for us so we just
(10)에 가장 가까운과 정액은 이전에 우리 단지를 우리에게 긴 해가 될 것 같다
have equal WX and we talked about the interpretations of this linear
동일 WX 가지고 우리는이 선형의 해석에 대해 이야기
classifier the fact that you can
당신이 할 수있는 그 사실을 분류
interpreted as matching templates or that you can interpret it as these
일치하는 템플릿으로 해석하거나 이들로 해석 할 수
images being in the very high-dimensional space and arlen your
및 매우 높은 차원 공간에있는 이미지를 사용자의 알렌
class partner kind of going in and coloring this space my class course so
클래스 파트너 종류의가는 그래서이 공간 내 수업 과정을 착색
to speak and so by the end of the class we got to this picture where we suppose
클래스의 말에 그렇게 말을하고 우리는 우리가 가정이 사진에 도착
we have a training example training dataset them just three images here
우리는 여기에서 훈련 예 훈련 데이터 세트들을 단지 세 개의 이미지가
along the columns and we have some classes say 10 classes and support n and
우리가 가지고있는 열을 따라 몇 가지 클래스 10 클래스와 지원 n은 말과
basically this function assigning scores for every single one of these images
기본적으로이 기능은 이러한 이미지의 모든 하나 하나에 대해 점수를 할당
with some particular setting off weights which have chosen randomly here we got
여기에 무작위로 선택한 일부 특정 설정 해제 무게를 우리는 가지고
some scores out and so some of these results are good and some of them are
아웃 등 일부 점수 결과 중 일부는 좋은 그들 중 일부는
bad so if you inspect this course for example in the first image you can see
첫 번째 이미지 예를 들어,이 과정을 검사하면 당신이 볼 수 있도록 나쁜
that the correct class or just cat got a score of 2.9 and that's kind of in the
올바른 클래스 또는 그냥 고양이는 2.9의 점수를 얻었고, 그것은에 가지 있다고
middle so some some classes he received a higher score which is not very good
중간 그래서 일부 일부 클래스는 그는 매우 좋지 않다 높은 점수를받은
some classes received a much lower score which is good for that particular image
일부 클래스는 특정 이미지에 좋은 훨씬 낮은 점수를받은
the car was very well classified because the car was much higher than all of the
차가 모두보다 높은 때문에 자동차 잘 분급
other ones and the Frog was enough durable classified all right so we have
다른 사람과 개구리는 내구성이 충분히 잘 그래서 우리는 모두 분류했다
this notion that four different weights these different weights work better or
이 개념 네 가지 무게 서로 다른 가중치가 작동하는지 더 나은 또는
worse on different images and of course we're trying to find a way it's that
다른 이미지에 물론 더 우리는이 것을의 방법을 찾기 위해 노력하고
give us course that are consistent with all the ground truth labels labels and
모든 지상 진실은 라벨 레이블과 함께 우리에게 일치 과정을 제공
the data and so what we're going to do now is so far with only I believe what I
데이터 그래서 우리가 지금 할 거 야하는에서만 지금까지입니다 내가 무엇을 믿는 I
just described like this is good and that's not so good and so on but we have
이 좋은 그 등등 그리 좋은 및하지만 우리가 같은 단지 설명
to actually give it a shot
실제로에게 총을주고
actually quantify this notion we have to say that this particular set of weights
실제로이 개념을 정량화 우리는 말을 그 무게의이 특별한 세트
WSA like 12 bad or 1.5 bad or whatever and then once we have this loss function
우리가이 손실 함수를 일단 다음 나쁜 12 1.5 나쁜이든과 같은 WSA
we're going to minimize it so we're going to find W that gets us the lowest
우리는 우리가 가장 낮은를 가져옵니다 W를 찾을거야, 그래서 우리는 그것을 최소화하기 위해거야
loss and we're going to look into that today we're going to look specifically
손실은 그리고 우리는 우리가 특별히 볼거야 오늘 조사거야
into how we can define a loss function that measures this unhappiness and then
그런 다음에이 불행 측정 손실 함수를 정의 할 수있는 방법
we're actually going to look at two different cases a boston soft max costs
우리는 실제로 두 개의 서로 다른 경우 보스턴 소프트 최대 비용 보는거야
costs and then we're going to look into the process optimization which is how do
비용과 우리는 어떻게되는 프로세스 최적화로 보는거야
you start off with these random audits and how do you actually find very very
이러한 임의의 감사로 시작하는 방법 당신은 실제로 아주 아주 찾을 수 있습니까
good sighting of weight sufficiently so I'm going to downsize this example that
체중을 잘 관찰을 충분히 그래서이 예제를 소형화거야 그
we have a nice working example to work with suppose we only had three classes
우리는 좋은 작업 예를 가정하는 작업을해야 우리는 세 가지 클래스가 있었다
and stuff you know
당신이 알고있는 물건
tens of thousands and we have these three images and these are our scores
수만 우리는이 세 가지 이미지가 이러한 우리의 점수입니다
for some setup W
일부 설치 W에 대한
we're going to now try to write down exactly our unhappiness with this result
우리는 지금이 결과를 정확히 우리의 불행을 작성하려고거야
of the first loss we're going to look into it is termed a multi-class SVM loss
첫 번째 손실 우리는 멀티 클래스 SVM 손실이라고한다 그것으로 볼거야
this is a generalization of a minority support vector machine that you may have
이것은 당신이 가질 수있는 소수 서포트 벡터 머신의 일반화이다
seen over the closest I think between 9 covers as well and so the setup here is
나뿐만 아니라 9 커버 사이에 생각하고 그렇게 설정이 여기에 가장 가까운을 통해 본
that we miss core function right so as a vector of Lacoste course these are our
우리는 라코스테의 벡터 물론 이러한 우리의있는 권리 있도록 핵심 기능 그리워 것을
inspectors and there's a specific term here
사찰단 특정 용어는 여기에있다
loss equal stew stuff and I'm going to interpret this loss now for Easter that
손실 동일 스튜 물건과 나는 부활절 지금이 손실을 해석하는거야 그
and we're going to see through a specific example of why this expression
우리는 왜 이런 식의 구체적인 예를 통해 볼거야
excess effectively what the SVM losses same is that it's something across all
초과 효과적으로 무엇 SVM 손실 같은 것은 모두에서 뭔가 있다는 것입니다
the incorrect examples so all the all the same across all the incorrect course
모든 잘못된 과정에 걸쳐 모두 모두 동일하므로 잘못된 예
classes so for every single example we have that loss and it's coming across
클래스는 하나 하나 예를 들어 우리는 그 손실을 그래서 그것을 가로 질러오고있다
all the incorrect classes and it's comparing the score at the core class
모든 잘못된 클래스와는 코어 클래스에서 점수를 비교하는 것
received in this court that the incorrect class receipt Jane minus s why
잘못된 클래스 영수증 제인은 마이너스 이유 다 것을이 법원에 접수
I why I being the correct label plus one and then that smacks of zero so what's
나는 왜 이렇게 무엇의 제로 난다 다음 올바른 레이블 더하기 하나 인
going on here as we're comparing the difference in this course and this
우리는이 과정이의 차이를 비교하는 여기에 계속
particular lost the same that not only do I want the correct score to be higher
특히이 같은 내가 올바른 점수가 높은 것으로 싶어 할뿐만 손실
than the incorrect score but there's actually a safety margin that we putting
잘못된 점수보다하지만 우리는 퍼팅 안전 마진은 실제로있다
on will put were using a safety margin
안전 마진을 사용하고 넣어 것입니다에
exactly one and we're going to go into why one makes sense to use as opposed to
정확히 하나의 우리는 반대로 사용하는 하나의 의미가 왜에 갈거야
some other hyper primary that we have to choose their and intuitively you can
우리가 자신을 선택해야하고 직관적으로 당신이 할 수있는 다른 하이퍼 차
look into notes for a much more rigorous derivation of exactly why that one
훨씬 더 엄격한 유도에 대한 메모를 들여다 정확히 왜 하나
doesn't matter but then too early to think about this underscores our kind of
중요하지만 이것에 대해 생각하는 다음 너무 일찍 우리의 종류를 강조하지 않습니다
scale-free because I can skim I W I can make it larger or smaller and you're
스케일이없는 내가 IWI을 탈지 할 수 있기 때문에 그것이 더 크거나 작게 만들 수 있으며있어
going to get larger or smaller course so really there's this pre-primary off
크거나 작은 코스를 얻기 위하여려고하는 것은 그래서 정말이 미리 차 떨어져있다
discourse and how large or small they can be that is tied to how large or
담론 방법 크거나 그들이 그렇게 할 수있는 작은이에 연결하는 방법 크거나
weights are in magnitude and so these whores are kind of arbitrary so using
무게는 크기에 등 사용하므로 이러한 창녀의 종류 임의적
one is just an arbitrary choice to some extent ok so let's see specifically how
하나는 확인 그래서 구체적으로 어떻게 볼 수 있도록 어느 정도 그냥 임의의 선택
this expression works with a concrete example so here I am going to evaluate
이 표현은 내가 평가하기 위하여려고하고 그래서 여기에 구체적인 예와 함께 작동
that loss for the first example so here we're competing for plugging in this
첫 번째 예를 들어 그 손실은 그래서 여기에 우리는이에 연결하기 위해 경쟁하고
course so we see that we're comparing
물론 그래서 우리는 우리가 비교하는 것을 볼 수
the score we got your car from 1-3 point to which is the correct class car and
올바른 클래스 자동차가있는 점수 우리가 1-3 점에서 당신의 차를 가지고있다하고,
then adding our safety margin of one and the maximum 0 and that is really what
다음 하나는 최대 0의 우리의 안전 마진을 추가하고 정말 무슨이다
it's doing is it's going to be clamping values 80 right so if we get a negative
그것은 값 (80)을 체결 할 것입니다하고있어 바로 우리가 부정적인 얻는 경우에 이렇게
result we're going to exclude VAT 0 so if you see the second class for the
당신이에 대한 두 번째 클래스를 참조하면 결과는 우리가 그렇게 VAT 0을 제외 할거야
incorrect Plaza frog
잘못된 플라자 개구리
1.7 subtracted from 3.2 at a safety margin and we gonna get to a point nine
1.7 안전 마진에서 3.2에서 차감 우리는거야 포인트 구에 도착
and then when you work this through you get a loss of 2.9
당신이 당신을 통해이 작업 할 때 다음 2.9의 손실을 가져
intuitively what you can see here the way this worked out is intuitively the
직관적으로 무엇을 당신이 밖으로 일을하는 방식이 직관적으로 여기 볼 수 있습니다
cat score is 3.2 so according to ESPN Los we would we would like ideally is
고양이 점수는 3.2 그래서 ESPN 로스에 따라 우리는 우리가 이상적으로 IS 싶은 것
that the scores for all the classes are up to it most
모든 클래스에 대한 점수는 최대 것을 가장
2.2 but the car class actually had much higher much higher score than one and
2.2 그러나 자동차 클래스는 실제로 한 것보다 훨씬 더 훨씬 더 높은 점수를했고,
this difference in what we would have liked which is 2.2 and what actually
우리가 어떤 좋아하는 것 무엇의 차이는 2.2 실제로 무엇인가
happened just like 11 is exactly this difference of 2.9 which is how bad of a
단지 11처럼 일하면 얼마나 나쁜 2.9의 바로이 차이
score outcome this was and in the other case in fraud case you can see the proc
결과를 점수이 였고, 사기 경우에 다른 경우에 당신은 시저를 볼 수 있습니다
score was quite a bit lower than low 2.2 and so the way that works out then the
점수는 낮은 2.2보다 상당히 낮은 다음 밖으로 작동하므로 방법이었다
math is that you end up getting a negative number when you compare this
수학은 당신이 비교할 때 음수를 받고 끝낼 것입니다
course and then the max 2000 lost contribution for that particular part
물론 다음 최대 2000은 특정 부분에 대한 공헌을 잃었다
and you end up with a loss of 2.9 oK so that's the loss for this first major for
즉,이 최초의 주요의 손실 그래서 당신은 2.9 확인의 손실로 끝날
the second image we're going to again do the same thing
두 번째 이미지는 우리는 다시 같은 일을 할거야
plug in the numbers were comparing the cats got the car score so we get my
고양이는 우리가 얻을 그래서 차 점수를 가지고 비교 한 숫자를 연결 내
point three months from 19 at a safety margin and the same for the other class
안전 마진과 다른 클래스의 동일한 19부터 3 개월간 포인트
so when you plug in your actually end up with a lot of zero and loss of 0
당신이에 연결하면하므로 실제로 0 제로의 많은 손실과 끝
intuitively is because the car score here is it is true that the car score is
여기에 자동차 점수이기 때문에 직관적으로는 자동차 점수 인 것은 사실이다
higher than all the others course for that image by at least one right that's
의 적어도 하나의 권리로 해당 이미지에 대한 모든 다른 코스보다 더 높은
why we got zero score 0 lost that is so the constraint was satisfied and some of
우리가 가진 이유 제로 점수 0은 너무 제약이 만족하고 일부이었다입니다 손실
their loss and in this case we end up with a very bad loss because of course
자신의 손실 때문에 우리가 물론 아주 나쁜 손실 끝이 경우
the frog class received a very low score but the other classes received quite
개구리 클래스는 매우 낮은 점수를 받았지만 다른 클래스는 아주 수신
high school so this adds up to an unhappiness of 10.9 and now if we
우리 경우 고등학교 그래서 이것은 지금 10.9의 불행까지 추가하고
actually want to combine all of this into a single loss function we're going
실제로 우리가 가고있는 하나의 손실 함수에이 모든 것을 결합하려는
to do the relatively intuitive transformation here we just take the
우리가 단지을 여기에 상대적으로 직관적 인 변환을 수행하는
average across all the losses we obtain
우리가 얻을 수있는 모든 손실에 걸쳐 평균
empower training set and so it would say that the loss at the end when you
트레이닝 세트 권한을 부여하고 그래서 말을 그 말에 손실 때를
average these numbers is 4.6 so this particular setting up w on this training
4.6 그래서이 특정 설정은이 훈련에 승까지이며이 숫자를 평균
data gives us some course which we plug into the loss function and we've given
데이터는 우리에게 우리가 손실 함수에 연결 몇 가지 과정을 제공하고 우리는 준
and unhappiness a four-point sex with this result ok so not going to ask you a
당신에게 부탁하지 않을 수 있도록 확인이 결과 4 점 섹스 대한 실망
series of questions to kind of test your understanding a bit about how this works
질문의 시리즈는 종류의이 어떻게 작동하는지에 대해 조금 이해를 테스트
I'll get into questions in a bit let me just pose my friend Michael questions
나는 나를 그냥 내 친구 마이클의 질문을 제기 할 수 있도록 약간의 질문에 얻을 것이다
first of all what if that's over there which is some overall the incorrect
우선 그 일부 전반적으로 잘못 인 저기 무슨 경우
colossus of Jane whatever that means that some overall the closest not just
제인의 거상 그 의미대로 일부 전반적으로 가장 가까운 그뿐만 아니라
the incorrect ones so what if we allowed J to equal to why I why am I actually
잘못된 사람은 그래서 우리는 J 내가 왜 실제로 I 오전 이유에 동일 할 수 있다면 무엇을
adding that small constraint in the summer there yes so in fact what would
사실이 네 그래서 여름에 그 작은 제약 조건을 추가하는 어떤 것
have happened is the reason the better gnite equal to I as if we allowed to I
일어난 우리는 I 허용 것처럼 I에 이유 더 나은 gnite 동일
then score of why I cancel reply
나는 답장을 취소 이유의 점수
you end up with a zero and really what you're doing is you're adding a constant
당신은 0으로 끝날 정말 당신이하는 일은 당신이 상수를 추가하는 것입니다
of London so if that someone's overall this course then really maybe just
런던의 그 누군가가이 과정은 정말 어쩌면 그냥 다음 전체 있도록 인 경우
completing the loss by constant of 10 that's why that's their second what if
그 두 번째 이유이다 (10)의 일정으로 손실을 완료 만약에
we used a mean instead of a sudden right so I'm summing up over all these
나는이 모든 이상 합산하고있어, 그래서 우리는 갑자기 오른쪽 대신 평균을 사용
constraints what if I used to mean just like I'm using mean to actually averaged
내가 평균 사용하고처럼 의미로 사용되는 경우 어떤 제약 실제로 평균합니다
over all the losses for all the examples what if I use the mean over this course
나는이 과정을 통해 평균을 사용하는 경우 어떤 모든 예제에 대한 모든 손실을 통해
the score concerns there were too many classes so you're right in that the
당신이 그에 맞아 있도록 점수 문제는 너무 많은 수업이 있었다
absolute value of the loss will be lower
손실의 절대 값이 낮은 것
a constant factor why
일정한 인자 이유
did actually do an average here would be averaging over the number of classes
실제로 여기에 평균을 했는가 클래스의 수에 걸쳐 평균 될 것이다
here but there's a constant number of classes say three in the specific
여기하지만 클래스의 상수가 특정 세 말의
example
예
amounts to putting constant of one-third in front of the loss and since we're
손실 앞의 3 분의 1의 상수를 넣어 금액 우리는에 있기 때문에
always in the end so that would make the Los lower just like you pointed out but
항상 결국 그래서 당신이 지적처럼 낮은 로스를 만들 것입니다하지만,
in the end what we're always interested in as we're going to minimize aw over
결국 우리는 항상 우리가 이상 아를 최소화거야로 관심
that loss so if you're shifting your lost by one or if you're scaling it with
그 손실은 그래서 만약 당신이 하나를 분실하거나 당신이 그것을 확장하는 경우 이동하고
a constant is actually doesn't change our solutions but you're still going to
일정은 당사의 솔루션을 변경하지 않습니다 실제로 있지만 여전히 갈거야
end up at the same optimal W so these choices are kind of basically free
그래서 이러한 선택이 가지 기본적으로 무료입니다 (W) 같은 최적의에서 결국
parameters doesn't matter so for convenience I'm adding do not equal to Y
매개 변수가 나는 Y와 동일하지 않습니다 추​​가 해요 편의를 위해 그렇게 중요하지 않습니다
and I'm not actually taken to mean although it's the same thing and the
나는 실제로이 같은 일을하고 비록 의미 촬영 아니에요
same goes for us for whether or not we average for some across the examples ok
같은 확인 우리가 예에서 일부 평균 여부를 우리에 간다
next question what if we instead used not to the formulation of there but a
우리가 대신 거기 제제하지만하지 사용되는 경우 어떤 다음 질문
very similar looking for inflation but there's an additional squared at the end
매우 유사 인플레이션을 찾고 있지만, 마지막에 제곱 추가있다
so we're taking the difference between course plus one this morning and then
그래서 우리는 물론 더하기 하나는 아침과의 차이를 취하고있어
were squaring that do we obtain the same or different lost when you think we
당신은 우리를 생각할 때 우리는 동일하거나 상이 손실을 얻을 않는 것이 제곱했다
obtain the same or different loss in a sense that if you were to optimize and
어떤 의미에서 동일하거나 상이 손실을받는 것이을 최적화한다면 및
find the best W do we get the same result or not
우리가 같은 결과를 얻는 가장 좋은 W를 찾을 여부
yes in fact get a different loss it's not as obvious to see but what one way
네, 사실 다른이 볼 등 명확하지의 손실 그러나 한 가지 방법을 얻을
to see it as that we're not just clearly scaling not just clearly scaling the Los
우리는 분명히 단지 명확 로스를 확장하지 확장하지 않는 것과 그것을 볼 수 있습니다
up or down by constant or shifting it by constant we're actually changing the
위 또는 일정하거나 우리가 실제로 변화하고 일정하여 이동 아래로
differences we are changing the tradeoffs nonlinearly in terms of how
차이점은 우리는 방법의 측면에서 비선형 장단점을 변경
the SVM support vector machines going to go there and trade all the different
SVM 지원 벡터 기계는 가서 모든 다른 무역 것
score margins in different examples but it's not obvious to see but basically
다른 예에서 여백을 점수하지만보고 분명 아니지만, 기본적으로
it's not very clear but I want to to illustrate that all changes to this loss
그것은 매우 분명하지 않다 그러나 나는이 손실에 대한 모든 변경 사항을 설명 할
are completely and the second permission here is in fact something we call a
완전하고 여기에 두 번째 권한은 사실 우리가 전화 뭔가
squared hinge loss instead of the one on top which recall hinge loss and you can
당신이 할 수있는 힌지 손실을 불러 상단에 대신 하나의 제곱 힌지 손실
use two different kind of hyper primarily 20 use most often you see the
주로 20 당신이 볼 가장 자주 사용하는 하이퍼 두 가지 다른 종류를 사용
first formulation that's what we use most of the time but sometimes you can
우리는 대부분의 시간을 사용하지만 때로는 당신이 할 수있는 무엇을 먼저 수립
see these assets with the square inch loss and better so that's something you
제곱 인치 손실이 자산을보고 더 나은 그래서 뭔가 당신입니다
play with that's really hyper primer but its most often used for the first one
그 정말 하이퍼 프라이머이다하지만 가장 자주 처음에 사용 플레이
let's also think about the scale of this loss was the min and max possible loss
이 손실의 규모가 최소 및 최대 가능 손실이었다에 대해의도 생각해 봅시다
that you can achieved with the multi-class SVM on your entire dataset
당신은 당신의 전체 데이터 세트에 다중 클래스 SVM을 달성 할 수
what is the smallest Mali
작은 말리 무엇인가
0 good what is the highest value so basically scores could be arbitrarily
점수를 임의로 될 수 기본적 있도록 가장 높은 값이 무엇인지 0 좋은
terrible so if you're signed score to the correct example is very very small
올바른 예 끔찍한 당신이 로그인 그래서 만약 점수는 매우 매우 작은
then you're going to get your loss going to infinity and one more question which
당신은 당신 무한대로가는 손실과 한 번 더 질문을받을거야하는
becomes kind of important when we start doing optimization usually when we
우리가 때 일반적으로 최적화를 수행 시작할 때 가지 중요
actually optimize these loss functions we start up with the initialization aw
실제로, 우리는 초기화 AW와 시동이 손실 함수를 최적화
that are very small weights so what ends up happening is that the scores at the
아주 작은 무게가 있기 때문에 무슨 일이 끝나는 것은 그에서 점수
very beginning of optimization are roughly near zero all of these are black
최적화의 처음에 가까운 검은 색이 모두 제로 대략있다
small numbers near zero so what are the loss when all these are new era in this
제로 근처의 작은 숫자는 그렇게 모든이의 새로운 시대 때 손실 무엇인가
particular case that's right number of classes minus 10 if all this course are
이 모든 과정이 있다면 바로 클래스의 수를 뺀 10의 특별한 경우
zero then he would this particular loss I put down here and by doing an average
제로 그는이 특정 손실 나는 평균을하고 여기에 의해 아래로 둘 것
across this way we would have achieved a loss of two ok so this is not very
이 아주없는 이러한 방식을 통해 우리는 확인이의 손실을 달성 한 것
important what's important is for safety checks when you're actually starting
당신이 실제로 시작 때 중요한 무엇이 중요한 안전 점검을위한
optimization and you're starting with very small numbers W and you print out
최적화는 당신은 W 매우 작은 숫자로 시작하고 당신은 인쇄
your first loss as you're talking about migration and you want to make sure that
당신이 있는지 확인하려면 당신이 이전에 대해 얘기로 첫 손실
you kind of understand the functional forms and that they can think through
당신은 종류의 기능 양식을 이해하고이를 생각할 수 있음
whether or not the number you get to make sense so I'm seeing to in this case
수 있는지 여부를 당신은 내가이 경우에 볼 수있어 너무 의미를 얻을
then I'm happy that the further losses may be implemented correctly percent
그때는 더 손실이 올바르게 %로 구현 될 수 있음을 행복 해요
sure but shortly certainly there's nothing wrong with it right away so it's
확실하지만 곧 확실히 잘못된 것은 바로이 그래서가 없습니다
interesting to think about these I'm going to go more into this loss of tiny
나는 작은이 손실에 더 갈거야이 생각하는 재미
bit but as a question in terms of the slide right now
비트하지만 지금 슬라이드의 관점에서 질문으로
question I was asked questions
질문 나는 질문했다
efficient to actually not have this constraint joy is not why I because it
실제로이 제약 기쁨이없는 것이 효율적이지 왜 그것 때문에
makes it more difficult to actually do these easy better eyes implementations
만드는 것이 더 어려워 실제로이 쉽게 더 눈 구현을 할 수
of this loss implementation so that actually predict my next slide to some
이 손실 구현의 실제로 일부 내 옆에 슬라이드를 예측할 수 있도록
degree so let me just going to say here sometime by code for Hollywood right out
정도는 그렇게 나를 바로 알아 할리우드의 코드에 의해 언젠가 여기에 말을하려고하자
to this loss function in the same here we're evaluating a lie in bed right now
여기에 같은이 손실 함수에 우리는 지금 침대에서 거짓말을 평가하고
we're getting a single example here so acts as a single column vector light is
하나의 열 벡터 빛이기 때문에 우리는 행동 때문에 여기에 하나의 예를 받고있어
an integer specifying the label and W is our weight matrix so what we do is we
정수 레이블을 지정하고 W는 우리가 우리가 할 그래서 우리의 가중치 행렬입니다
validate this course which is just a couple times X then we compute these
단지 몇 시간의 X는 그리고 우리는 이러한 계산이다이 과정을 확인
margins which is the difference between the course we obtained and the correct
우리가 획득 과정 올바른 간의 차이 마진
score + 10 these are numbers between 0 and whatever and then see this dish
점수 + 10이 0에서 무엇이든 다음이 접시를 볼 사이의 번호는
online margins that y equals 0 YZ them there
온라인 여백 Y가 0 YZ 그와 같
yeah exactly so basically I'm doing this efficient backgrounds importation which
그래 정확히 그래서 기본적으로 나는이 효율적인 배경 수입을하고있어 어떤
goes to your point and then I want to embrace that margin there because I'm
당신의 포인트로 이동 한 다음 내가이기 때문에이 그 여백을 수용 할
certain that margin said why currently has one and I don't want to inflate my
현재 하나를 가지고 있는데이 팽창하지 않는 이유 이익률은 말했다 어떤 것을 내
score and so I'll set at 20
점수 그리고 나는 20로 설정합니다
yes I suppose you could subtract one of the end as well so we can optimize if we
그래 나는 우리가 경우에 최적화 할 수 있도록뿐만 아니라 말을 뺄 수도있을 것 같군요 우리
want but we're not going to think about this too much if you do if you do in
원하지만 우리는 너무 많은 당신이 할 경우, 당신이 할 경우이에 대해 생각하지 않을거야
your assignment that's very welcome for extreme punishments and there were some
극단적 인 처벌에 대한 매우 환영의 일부가되었다 과제
of those markets and so we got lost going back to the site anymore questions
그 시장 그리고 우리는 더 이상 다시 사이트에 질문에가는 길을 잃었다
about this formulation and by the way this formulation if you wanted to make
이 제제에 대해 당신이 만들고 싶어하는 경우 방법이 제제에 의해
it if you actually write it down for just two closest you'll see that it
당신은 실제로 두 가장 가까운 당신이 그것을 볼 수 있습니다 그것을 아래로 작성하는 경우
reduces to a minor support vector machine lost ok so we'll see a different
우리가 다른를 볼 수 있도록 확인 잃은 작은 서포트 벡터 머신에 감소
function soon and then we're going to look at the comparisons of them as well
기능은 곧 다음 우리는뿐만 아니라 이들의 비교에서 볼거야
but for now actually so at this point what we have is we have this
하지만 지금은 실제로 우리가 가지고있는이 시점에서 우리가 이것을 가지고있다
wrapping up its course and then we have this loss function which have not
그 과정을 마무리하고 우리는하지 않은이 손실 함수를
written out and its full form where we have these differences between this
써 우리는이 사이에 이러한 차이가 자사의 전체 형태
course +1 some of her closest and the Sun and the average across hold examples
물론 한 그녀의 가장 가까운과 태양과 홀드 예에서 평균의 일부
right so that's the loss function right now I'd like to convince you that
즉 지금 손실 함수를 그건 바로 그래서 내가 당신을 설득하고 싶습니다
there's actually a bug with this loss function in other words if I'd like to
내가하고 싶은 경우 즉이 손실 함수에 버그가 실제로있다
use this loss on Sunday as in practice I might get some not very nice properties
나는 매우 좋은하지 속성을 얻을 수 있습니다 연습과 일요일이 손실을 사용
ok if this if this was the only thing I was using my phone and it's not
이이 경우는 내 전화를 사용하고있는 유일한이었고, 경우 확인이 아니에요
completely obvious to see exactly what the issue is so I'll give you guys a
정확히 문제가 너무 무엇인지보고 완전히 분명 내가 너희들을 줄 것이다
hint in particular suppose that we found the W
특히 힌트는 우리가 W를 발견한다고 가정
getting zero loss ok on something and now the question is is this w unique or
뭔가에 제로 손실을 확인 받고 이제 문제는 것은이 w 고유하거나
face another way can you give me aww that would be different but also
다른 방법에 직면 당신이 내게 줄 수 앗 그 또한 다를 수 있지만 것
definitely achieve zero loss in the back
확실히 다시 제로 손실을 달성
that's right and so you're saying we can scale it by some constant and in
맞아 그래서 당신은 우리가 어떤 상수와 그것을 확장 할 수있는 말을하는지
particular all formats are based on constraint you probably want to meet
특히 모든 형식은 아마의 만남을 원하는 제약 조건을 기반으로
young greater than one right so basically what I can do as I can change
젊은 내가 변경할 수있는 내가 할 수있는 권리 그래서 기본적으로 1보다 큰
my weight and make them larger and larger all I would be doing is I'm just
내 무게와 내가 일을 할 수있는 모든 난 그냥 해요입니다 그들이 더 크고 더 크게 만들
create making the score differences larger and larger as I came up w right
내가 바로 승 등장하면서 점수 차이가 크고 큰 만들기 만들
because of the liquor law sport here so basically it's not a very desirable
여기 그래서 기본적으로 주류 법 스포츠의 그것은 매우 바람직하지 때문에
property because we have the entire subspace of W that is optimal and all of
부동산 우리는 최적의 및 모든 인 W의 전체 부분 공간을 가지고 있기 때문에
them are according to this loss function completely the same but intuitively
그것들이 손실 함수에 따라되는 완전히 동일하지만, 직감적
that's not what I can burn as property to pass and so just to see this in
그게 내가 전달하는 속성으로 구울 수 있고, 그래서 그냥이를 볼 게 아니에요
america to convince yourself that this is the case I taking this example of
미국이 내가이 예를 복용하는 경우가 있음을 자신을 설득
what we achieved previously 0 loss there before and I suppose I W I twice I mean
나는 두 번 내 말은 IWI을 가정 해 우리가 전에이 이전에 0 손실을 달성
this is a very simple math going on here but basically I would be conflicting or
여기 아주 간단한 수학이다 일어나고 있지만, 기본적으로 내가 충돌 할 수 또는 것
my scores by two times and so their difference would also becomes larger so
내 점수 두 배 그래서 그 차이는 매우 커진다 것
if all your score differences inside the max 50 well already negative then
최대 50 아니라 내부의 모든 점수 차이 이미 부정적인 경우
there's going to become more and more negative and so you end up with larger
이 점점 더 부정적이 될 것 그래서 당신은 더 큰 끝낼 것
and larger negative values inside them access and just become zero all the time
더 큰 음의 값 접근을 그들에게 내부와 단지 제로 모든 시간이 될
but the scale factor would have to be larger than 1 because
그러나 스케일 팩터는 1보다 크게 할 것이기 때문에
another question for simplicity but yeah basically scores are WX + be so so
단순성에 대한 또 다른 질문하지만 그래 기본적으로 점수는 WX가 + 그래서 그렇게 될 수 있습니다
you're just yet
당신은 아직이야
forget to buy some just chillin W myself ok so the way to fix this is intuitively
W 일부 단지 어때을 구입하는 것을 잊지 자신이 문제를 해결하는 방법이 직관적 그래서 확인
we have this entire subway some W's and it all works the same according to this
우리는이 전체 지하철 몇 W의를 가지고 모든이에 따라 동일하게 작동
loss function and what we'd like to do as we'd like to have a preference over
손실 함수와 우리가 환경 설정을 통해이하고 싶은대로 우리가하고 싶습니다
some W's over others just based on intrinsic you know what what do we
일부 W의 이상 다른 사람이 단지 고유에 따라 당신은 우리가 무엇을 알고
desire of W to look like forget the data is just what what are nice things to
데이터를 잊지 같이하는 W의 욕망에 좋은 일이 무엇 것입니다
happen and so this introduces the notion of regularization which we're going to
일이 그래서 이것은 우리가가는거야 정규화의 개념을 소개합니다
be attending to our loss function so we have an additional term there which is
우리가하는 추가 용어를 그래서 우리의 손실 함수에 참석
land up times a regularization function of W and the regularization function
W의 정규화 기능과 정규화 작동 시간을 착륙
measures the niceness of your W ok and so we don't only want to fit the data
확인을 W의 쾌적을 측정하고 그래서 우리는 단지 데이터에 맞게 싶지 않아
but we also won W to be nice and we're going to see some ways of framing that
그러나 우리는 또한 좋은 것으로 W를 원하고 우리는 프레임의 몇 가지 방법을 보게 될 것입니다 그
exactly why they make sense and into going on as regularization has a way of
정확히 왜 그들이 이해와 정규화로가는로하는 방법이있다
trading off your training act your training loss and your generalization
훈련 떨어져 거래는 훈련 손실 및 일반화 행동
lost on a test set so intuitively regularization a set of techniques where
그래서 직관적으로 설정 테스트에 손실은 기술 곳의 세트를 정규화
we're adding objectives to the loss which will be fighting with this guy so
우리는이 사람과 싸우게 될 것이다 손실에 목표를 추가하고 그래서
this guy just wants to fit your training data and that guy once W to look some
이 사람은 당신의 훈련 데이터에 맞게 원하는 한 번 W 그 사람은 몇 가지를보고
particular way and so they're fighting each other sometimes in your objective
특정 방식 그래서 그들은 당신의 목적에 때로는 서로 싸우고있어
because we want to simultaneously achieve both of them but it turns out
우리는 동시에 모두 달성하고자하지만 밝혀 때문에
that adding these regularization techniques even if it makes your
이러한 정규화 기술을 추가하는 것은 그것을 만드는 경우에도 귀하
training error worse so we're not correctly classifying examples which he
교육 에러가 악화 그래서 우리는 제대로 예를 분류하지 않는 한 그
noticed is that the test set performance and something better and we'll see an
주의는 테스트 세트 성능과 더 나은 뭔가 우리가를 볼 수 있다는 것입니다
example of why that might be actually what the next for now I just want to
그 내용은 다음 지금 난 그냥 원하는 것을 실제로 할 수있는 이유의 예
point out the next light but for now I just want to point out that the most
다음 빛을 지적하지만 지금 난 그냥 가장 지적하고 싶은
common form of realization is the what we call to regularization or weight
실현의 일반적인 형태는 우리가 정규화 또는 중량에 전화를 무엇
decay and really what we're doing is suppose W in this case is a 2d matrix so
부패와 정말 우리가이 경우 W 생각되는 일을하는지 그래서 2 차원 행렬
I had to some Sauveur que el the rows and columns that really is just
좀 뵈르 가야 엘에 정말있는 행과 열을했다
element wise W squared
제곱 W 현명한 요소
and we're just putting them all into the Los ok so this this particular
우리는 로스 확인되므로이이 특정에 그들 모두를 가하고있어
regulation it likes w's to be 0 right so when WS all 09 realization is happy but
이 승 좋아하는 규정은 모든 09 실현 행복 WS을 때 바로 그렇게 공을 수있어하지만
of course you can't people there because then you can classify so these guys will
물론 당신은 당신은 그래서이 사람들이 의지가없는 사람을 분류 할 수 있기 때문에
fight each other there are different forms of regularization with different
서로 싸울 다른과 정규화의 다른 형태가있다
approaching Kong's will go into some of them much later in the class and I just
홍콩의 클래스에 훨씬 나중에 그들 중 일부에 가서 그냥 것 접근
like the 2nd Lt regularization is the most common form and that's what you'll
2 중위 정규화가 가장 흔한 형태이며, 그처럼 당신은 무엇을거야
use quite often in this class as well it's not like to convince you I'd like
이 클래스에서 자주 사용뿐만 아니라 내가 원하는 당신을 설득 같지
to convince you that this is a reasonable thing to want out of it w
당신을 설득하면이 승 그것에서 할 수있는 합리적인 것입니다
that its weights are small so consider this very simple cooked up example to
그래서이 매우 간단 위로 요리 예를 고려의 무게가 작은 것을
get the intuition suppose we have an example where we are in four-dimensional
우리는 네 가지 차원에서 어디에 직관은 우리가 예를 들어 있다고 가정하세요
space where we're doing this classification and we have an even
우리는이 분류를하고있는 우리는 심지어이 공간
better off just all once X and now suppose we have these two candidates
그냥 한꺼번에 X 나을 지금 생각 우리는이 두 후보가
weight matrices or wait
체중 행렬 또는 대기
single voice I suppose to right now so one of them is 100 and the other is 25
I 지금까지 가정 단일 음성 때문에 그 중 하나 (100)이고 다른 하나는 25
everywhere since we have in your loss functions you'll see that their effects
우리는 당신의 손실 함수에있는 사방 이후 자신의 효과를 볼 수 있습니다
are the same so basically have a leading scorer is by WX so the doc product with
같은 그래서 기본적으로 선도적 득점이 문서 제품과 있도록 WX입니다 가지고 있습니다
ex is identical for both of these discourse with both of these but
예는이 두 그러나 이러한 담론의 모두에 대해 동일
regularization with strictly favor one of these over the other which one with
엄격와 정규화는 다른 통해 이들 중 하나를 선호하는 하나
the regularization cost favor even though their effects are the same which
정규화 선정 호의 그 효과는 동일 할지라도
one is better in terms of realization the second one right and so the
하나는 실현의 관점에서 그래서 두 번째 오른쪽 낫다
regularization would tell you that even though they're achieving the same
정규화는 동일한을 달성하는 경우에도 당신을 말할 것
effects in terms of the data loss classification down the road we actually
도로 실제로 우리 다운 데이터 손실 분류면에서 효과
significantly preferred the second one what's better about the second one is
크게 두 번째가에 대한 더 나은 무엇 두 번째를 선호
that a good idea to have
좋은 생각 가지고하는 것이
that's correct so well that's one interpretation I like the most is well
그는 내가 가장 좋아하는 하나의 해석이 잘 있어요 잘 맞습니다
it takes into account the most number of things in your X Factor right so what
그것은 바로 그래서 당신의 X 팩터에서 고려 사물의 가장 많은 무엇이
this Delta realization wants to do is to spread out your WSUS as much as possible
이 델타 실현하고 싶어 가능한 한 많은 당신의 WSUS를 확산하는 것입니다
so that you're taking into account all the input features are only empathic
당신이 고려하고 있도록 모든 입력 기능은 공감이다
sauce and wants to use as much as many other dimensions as it likes its a
소스와는 자사을 좋아하는만큼 많은 다른 차원을 사용하고 싶어
cheating the same effect
동일한 효과를 부정
intuitively speaking and so that's better than just focusing on just one
직관적으로 말하기, 그래서 그것은 단지 하나에 집중보다 낫다
dimension is just nice it's something that often works in practice basically
차원은 종종 기본적으로 실제로 작동 뭔가 그냥 좋은
just the way things are and biggest arranged and the property that they
다만 방법의 일이며 가장 큰 배열 속성 그들이
usually have to tackle any questions about the regularization good idea
일반적으로 정규화 좋은 아이디어에 대한 질문이 해결해야
everyone has sold some basically our losses will always have this forum where
모든 사람이 어떤 기본적으로 우리의 손실이 항상이 포럼 곳이있을 것이다 판매했다
we we have a dinner loss and they will also have a regularization it's a very
우리는 저녁 식사 손실을 가지고 있고 또한 매우이다 정규화를해야합니다
common thing to have in practice ok I'm not going to go into the second
실제로 가지고 일반적인 것은 좋아 내가 두 번째로 이동하지 않을거야
classifier pacifier and we'll see some differences between the US and support
분류 젖꼭지와 우리는 미국과 지원 사이에 약간의 차이를 볼 수 있습니다
vector machine and this soft mask classifier in practice these are kind of
벡터 머신과 실천이 부드러운 마스크 분류 이러한 종류의 수 있습니다
like these two choices that you can have either a spam or something like the most
이 두 가지 선택처럼 당신이 가장 좋아 스팸 또는 뭔가를 가질 수
commonly used linear classifiers often you'll see that so far as preferred and
선호로 일반적으로 지금까지 자주 당신이 나타납니다 선형 분류를 사용
I'm not exactly sure why because usually the end up working about the same and I
나는 정확히 모르겠어요 왜 같은 난에 대해 작업 보통 말까지 있기 때문에
just like to mention that this is also sometimes called multnomah was just
다만이 또한 때때로라고 멀티 그냥 것을 말씀 드리고
aggression so if you're familiar with logistic regression this is just the
침략 당신은 로지스틱 회귀에 대해 잘 알고 있다면이 그냥 그래서
generalization of it into multiple dimensions or in this case multiple
여러 차원으로 또는이 경우 여러에 그것의 일반화
clouds of smoke just as they're questioned over there
연기의 구름은 저쪽에 의문을 제기하는 것처럼
why do we want to use if we'd like to pick between them in some way and I
왜 우리는 우리가 어떤 식 으로든 내가 그들 사이에서 선택하려는 경우 사용하려는
think we are going for is that one thing low W us is a reasonable way to pick
우리가 선택하는 합리적인 방법입니다 (W) 우리가 갈 생각은 한 가지 낮다
among men and the ultra-right favor diffuse w's like in this case here and
남자와 울트라 오른쪽 호의 확산 중 여기이 경우처럼 W 및
one of the intuitive ways in which I can try to pitch why this is a good idea is
나는 피치 시도 할 수있는 직관적 인 방법 중 하나는 왜이 좋은 생각입니다
that diffuse weights basically see this w one is completely ignoring your inputs
그 확산 가중치는 기본적으로 하나의 승를 확인 완전히 입력을 무시
to three and four but W two is using all of the inputs right because of the way
셋, 넷하지만 W이 오른쪽 방식 때문에의 입력을 모두 사용
to defuse and so intuitively this just end up usually working better at a test
완화 등 직관적으로 이것은 단지 보통 테스트에서 더 나은 작업을 끝낼 수 있습니다
I'm because more evidence is being accumulated and your decisions instead
더 많은 증거가 대신 축적하고 결정되고 있기 때문에 난
of just one single evidence one single feature that's right
단 하나의 증거 하나의 기능으로 맞아
that's right that's right so the idea here is that these two W 110 w to
맞아 맞아 그래서 아이디어는 여기입니다의 두 110 W에 w 그
achieving the same effect so this data loss suppose that that's basically it
동일한 효과를 얻기 때문에이 데이터 손실은 기본적으로 있다고 가정
doesn't care between the two but the regularization expressed a preference
두 정규화 그러나 사이에 상관하지 않는 환경 설정을 표시
for them and since we had any objective and we're going to end up optimizing
우리가 어떤 목표를 가지고 있었고, 때문에 우리는 최적화 끝날거야 그들과
over this loss functions are going to find the W that simultaneously
이 손실을 통해 기능은 동시에 W를 찾을거야
accomplishes both of those and so we end up aw that not only classified correctly
그 모두를 수행 그래서 우리는 제대로 분류되지 않은 아우를 종료
but we also have the added preference that actually wanted to be and we wanted
그러나 우리는 또한 실제로 싶었다 추가 환경 설정을 가지고 우리는 원
to be diffuse as much as possible could also be indifferent L one has some nice
또한 무관심 L의 하나가 될 수있는 가능한 한 많이 확산 될 것은 멋진이
properties which I don't want to go into right now we might cover it later fell
나는에 가고 싶지 않아 속성 지금 우리는 나중에 떨어졌다 덮을 수 있습니다
one has some properties like a sparsity inducing properties what if you end up
하나는 당신이 끝날 경우 어떤 속성을 유도 희소성과 같은 몇 가지 특성을 가지고
having lunch in your objectives you'll find that lots of W's will end up being
당신의 목표에서 점심을 먹고는 W의 많은이 끝나게 것을 확인할 수 있습니다
exactly zero for reasons that we might go into labor and that sometimes is like
정확히 제로 우리가 노동에 갈 수도하고 때로는 같다 이유
a feature selection almost and so I'll one is another alternative that we might
기능 선택은 거의 그리고 나는 하나는 우리가 수도 또 다른 대안 인 것이다
go into a bit more later
더 이상 조금로 이동
that isn't it may be a good thing that were ignoring features and just using
즉, 기능을 무시하고 그냥 사용하고 좋은 일이 될 수 없습니다
one of them yeah there's many technical reasons why realization is a good idea I
실현 좋은 생각 나는 이유 중 하나는 그래 많은 기술적 인 이유가있다
went to give you just basic intuition so maybe maybe tell them that but I think
당신은 단지 기본적인 직관을주고 갔다 그래서 어쩌면 어쩌면하지만 내가 생각하는 그들에게 그 말
that's a fair point if I have a good return I would have to be ignoring some
그게 내가 좋은 수익을 만약 내가 일부를 무시되어야 할 것이다 공정한 점이다
and looking at times and learning theory and you saw some of that in 229 and
때때로보고 이론을 학습하고 229에 그 중 일부를보고
there are some results on white regularization is a good case in in
흰색 정규화에 대한 몇 가지 결과는 거기에서 좋은 사례가되고있다
those areas and I don't think I'm gonna go into that and salt also beyond the
그 지역과 나는거야 생각하지 않습니다이 넘어도 그에 가서 소금
scope of this class so far this class just altering our nation will make your
이 클래스의 범위 지금까지이 클래스는 것 우리의 국가를 변경하여
test error better someone to go to satisfy to find out which is just
테스트 오류 나은 사람은 어떤 알 수 만족시키기 위해 이동
generalization of logistic regression to the way the way this will work as this
방법에 대한 로지스틱 회귀 분석의 일반화는이 같은 작동 방식
is just a different functional form for how loss is specified on top of these
손실이 위에 지정된 방법에 대한 그냥 다른 함수 형태입니다
course some particular there's this interpretation that classifier puts on
분류가 박았 물론 일부 특정 이러한 해석이있다
top of this course these are not just some arbitrary scores and we want to
이 과정의 상단이는 어떤 임의의 점수가 아니며, 우리가 원하는
margins to be met but we have specific interpretation that is maybe more
마진이 충족되어야합니다하지만 우리는 어쩌면 더 구체적인 해석이
principled kind of from a problem that point of view where we actually
보기의 문제에서 그 시점 어디에 실제로 우리의 원칙 종류
interpret these course not just as these things that mean margins but these are
그냥 여백을 의미하지만, 이러한는 이러한 것들을로하지 이러한 과정을 해석
actually the normalized lock probabilities that are assigned to
에 할당 된 실제 정규화 된 잠금 확률
different classes ok so we're going to go into exactly what this means in a bit
다른 클래스는 확인 그래서 우리는이 조금 의미 정확히 무엇에 갈거야
these are normalized lock probabilities of all the twice given the image in
이러한 모든 회 주어진 이미지의 정규화 로크 확률의
other words we are assuming that the scores are unlike problem peace than the
즉 우리는 점수가보다 문제의 평화와 달리 것을 가정합니다
way to get probabilities of the closest like Sasuke is that we take these the
사스케와 같은 가장 가까운 확률을 얻을 수있는 방법은 우리가이을 것입니다
score
점수
exponential all of them to get the anomalous probabilities and we normalize
변칙 확률을 얻기 위해 그들 모두를 기하 급수적으로 우리는 정상화
them to get them to normalize probabilities so we divided by the sum
우리가 합으로 나눈 있도록 그들에게 그들이 확률 정상화를 얻을 수
over all the exponential its course and that's how we actually get this
모든 지수의 과정을 통해 그 우리가 실제로 얻을 방법
expression for a probability of a class given the image and so this function
클래스의 확률에 대한 표현은 이미지 등이 기능을 부여
here is called a soft max function if you see if someone has to eat to them
당신이 누군가가 그들에게 먹을 경우 참조하는 경우 여기에 부드러운 최대 함수를 호출한다
the elements are currently interested in divided by the sum overall expense sheet
요소가 합 전반적인 비용 매로 나눈 현재 관심
its course that's the way this will work basically is if we're in this problem
우리는이 문제에 있다면이 기본적으로 작동 할 방법의 과정이다
premark we're really lucky
premark 우리는 정말 운이 좋다
that we're deciding that this is the probability of different classes that
우리는 이것이 다른 클래스의 확률 것을 결정하고 있다는 것을
makes sense in terms of what you what you really want to do in this setting
당신이 정말이 설정에서 수행 할 작업을 어떤 측면에서 의미가 있습니다
will probably over different classes one of these is correct so we wanted to
것입니다 아마 다른 클래스를 통해 이들 중 하나는 우리가 원 정확
maximize the log-likelihood
로그 우도를 최대화
for the loss function and so we want to maximize the log likelihood of the true
손실 함수 등등을 위해 우리는 실제의 로그 우도를 최대화 할
class and since we're running a loss function we want to minimize the
클래스와 우리가 손실 함수를 실행하고 있기 때문에 우리는을 최소화하려면
negative log-likelihood of the true class ok so you end up with a series of
진정한 클래스의 음의 로그 우도 확인이 일련의와 끝까지 그렇게
expressions here really are lost function as you want the log-likelihood
로그-가능성을 원하는대로 여기 표현은 정말 기능을 잃게됩니다
the correct class to be high so negative of it want to be low and the
올바른 클래스는 너무 부정적인 높은 낮은 싶어하는
log-likelihood is some expansion of course let's look at a specific example
로그인 가능성이 코스의 일부 확장되어 이제 구체적인 예를 살펴 보자
to make this more later here I actually like something that expression so that
실제로 있도록 표현 뭔가처럼 나중에 여기에 내가이 더 만들려​​면
this is the Los negative log that expression let's look at how this
이 표현의 방법이 살펴 보겠습니다하는 로스 음의 로그입니다
expression works and I think it'll give you a better intuition know exactly what
표현은 작품과 내가 아는 당신에게 더 나은 직관을주지 생각을 정확히
this is doing lights what's computing so suppose here we haven't these scores
이것은 우리가이 점수를하지 않은 여기에 가정 그래서 컴퓨팅 있는지 등을하고있다
that came out from our neural network or from our earlier pacifier and these are
즉, 우리의 신경 네트워크 또는 우리의 이전 젖꼭지에서 나온 이들이다
the unlock problem peace so as I mentioned we want to exponentially them
내가 언급 한 바와 같이 그렇게 잠금 해제 문제의 평화 우리는 기하 급수적으로 그들을 원하는
first because under this interpretation that gives us the normalized
첫 번째 때문에 우리에게 정규화를 제공이 해석에서
probabilities and now he's always some 21 so we have two divided by the sum of
확률과 우리가 두 가지의 합으로 나눈 값이 지금은 항상 일부 (21)의
all of these so we add up these guys and we divide to actually get probably out
이 모든 그래서 우리는이 사람을 추가하고 우리가 실제로 아마 아웃을 얻기 위해 분할
under this interpretation we've carried out the set of transformations and what
이 해석에서 우리는 변환 어떤 세트를 수행 한
this is saying is that this interpretation the probability assigned
말하는이이 해석은 확률 할당 된 것입니다
to this image of being a cat is 13% car is 87% and progress very unlikely 0%
고양이가되는이 이미지에 13 %의 차량이 87 % 진행 매우 가능성이 0 %입니다
these are the probabilities and not normally in the setting you want to
이러한 확률이며,하지 일반적으로 설정하는 당신이 원하는
maximize the lock probability because it turns out that maximizing just a rock
그냥 바위를 극대화 밝혀 때문에 잠금 확률을 극대화
probability is not as nice mathematically so lonely you see
확률은 수학적으로 볼 그래서 외로운으로 좋은하지 않습니다
maximizing luck probabilities and then so you want to minimize the probability
당신이 확률을 최소화 할 수 있도록 다음 행운의 확률을 극대화
so the correct class here is cat which is only having 13 percent chance
그래서 여기에 올바른 클래스는 13 %의 확률을 가지고있다 고양이는
Anderson misinterpretation so negative log of points 13 gets us 89 and so
포인트 13 앤더슨 오해 때문에 음의 로그가 우리를 얻을 수 89 등
that's the final to find a loss that we would achieve for this class here under
그것은 우리가 아래에 여기에이 클래스 달성 할 손실을 찾을 수있는 마지막이다
this interpretation of a classifier so
분류기의이 해석 때문에 29
let's go over some examples were some questions now related to this to try to
의 몇 가지 예에 시도하는 지금이 관련된 몇 가지 질문을했다 통해 가자
interpret exactly how this works
이 작품 정확히 어떻게 해석
first I was the min and max possible lost with this loss function so that the
처음 나는 그래서이 손실 기능을 잃은 분 가능한 최대이었다
loss function what is the smallest Mali and the highest body has to think about
손실 함수 어떤 작은 말리이며, 가장 높은 몸은 생각한다
this what is the smallest value that we can cheap zero and how would that happen
이것은 우리가 싼 제로하고 어떻게 일어날 수있는 가장 작은 값 것입니다
I can get so if you're correct class is getting probably have one where we have
당신은 우리가 하나가 올바른 클래스 아마지고 있다면 나는 그렇게 얻을 수 있습니다
a one was replying to the law and we're getting negative log of 110 and the
하나는 법에 회신하고 우리는 (110)과의 음의 로그를 받고있어
highest possible loss so just as well as we were getting the same 0 is minimum
그래서 그냥뿐만 아니라 우리는 같은 공을 받고 있었다으로 가장 높은 손실이 최소
and infinite is maximum so infant loss would be achieved if you end up giving
무한 당신이주는 끝날 경우 최대 그래서 유아 손실을 달성 할 것입니다
your cat score very tiny probability and then log of 0 gives you negative
0 당신이 부정적인 제공의 고양이는 아주 작은 확률을 득점 한 후 로그인
infinity so negative that is just the infinite so yeah so the same balance as
그래서 그래 그래서 같은 균형으로 바로 무한 무한 그래서 음
p.m. and also this question
오후이 질문
normally when we initialize W with roughly small small weights wind up with
우리는 대략 작은 작은 무게와 W를 초기화 할 때 일반적으로 바람
all these cars are nearly zero what ends up being the loss in this case
모든 자동차는 거의이 경우 손실 될 수있을 테니까요 무엇 제로되어
checks at the beginning of your optimization what do you expect to see
당신이보고 기대 무슨 최적화의 시작 부분에 체크
as your first loss
첫 번째 손실
one over a number of classes so you may be getting older is here you get to all
나이가 점점 될 수 있도록 클래스의 수에 하나 당신이 모든에 도착 여기
of one's here and so here is one over a number of classes and then they get a
한 다음 여기 그래서 여기에 클래스의 수에 하나입니다 그리고 그들은 얻을
blog about and something your final awesome so actually for myself whenever
에 대한 블로그를 자신 할 때마다 대한 그래서 실제로 최종 멋진 뭔가
I run up my station I sometimes take note of my number of classes and I
나는 때때로 클래스와 I의 내 번호 주목을 내 스테이션을 실행
evaluate negative log one of a number of classes and I'm trying to see what is
클래스의 숫자 중 하나를 부정 로그 평가하고 내가 무엇을보고 노력하고있어
the my first beginning lost expect and so when I start up my decision I make
잃어버린 내 첫 시작은 기대와 내 결정을 시작할 때 그래서 나는 확인
sure that I'm getting roughly that otherwise I know some things may be
확실히 내가 아는 다른 몇 가지가있을 수 있음을 대략 얻고 있음
slightly off expect to get something on that order
약간 떨어져 순서에 뭔가를 얻을 것으로 예상
moreover as an optimizing expect that I go from thats 20 and if I'm seeing
또한 최적화 나는 20 그게 전부에서 가서 제가 보는 경우 기대
negative numbers then I know from the functional form that something very
음수는 내가 함수 형태 알고 뭔가 매우
strange is going on right
이상은 오른쪽에있는 것입니다
never actually expected gonna give numbers out of this assault max loss
실제로 예상하지거야이 폭행 최대 손실에서 번호를 부여
I'll show you one more slide nothing some questions just to reiterate the
몇 가지 질문 단지를 반복하는 당신에게 또 하나의 슬라이드 아무것도 표시되지 것입니다
difference between them and really what they look like as we have the score
그들과 정말 그들이 우리가 점수를 가지고있는 모습의 차이
function which gives aw we get our scores of actor and now the difference
차이 지금 우리가 배우의 우리의 점수를 얻을 아​​와를 제공 기능
is just how they interpret what these course coming out from this function is
그들은이 함수에서 나오는 이러한 과정이 무엇인지 해석하는 방법을 그냥
so I just ran its course no interpretation whatsoever we just want
그래서 난 그냥 무엇이든지 우리가 원하는 어떤 해석의 과정을 실행하지
that a lot of a larger score the correct score to be some margin above the
더 큰 점수 정확한 점수를 많이 위의 몇 가지 한계가 될 것을
incorrect course or interpreted to be these unless lott probabilities and then
잘못된 과정이나 해석은 로트 확률과하지 않는 한이 될 수 있습니다
in this framework we first went to get the probabilities and then we want to
이 프레임 워크에서 우리는 먼저 확률을 가져 갔고, 우리는 원하는
maximize the public in the crack losses or the log of them and so that ends up
균열 손실의 공개 또는 이들의 로그를 극대화하고 그래서 그 끝
giving us the loss function or something so they start off at the same way but
우리에게 손실 함수 또는 무언가를주는 동일한 방법에서 시작하도록하지만,
they just happened to get to the difference less results we're going to
그들은 단지 우리가 가고있는 차이가 적은 결과를 얻을 수 있었
exactly what the differences are in a bit there are questions
정확히 차이가 조금에서 어떤 질문이 있습니다
they take your classified as near instantaneous to evaluate most of the
그들은 대부분을 평가하는 순간 근처로 분류을
work is done in the convolutions and so will see that the classifier and
작품은 회선에서 수행되고, 그렇게 볼 것이다 분류 및
especially the losses roughly the same of course South max involve some XP and
물론 남한 최대의 거의 같은 특히 손실이 수반 일부 XP 및
so on so these operations are slightly more expensive perhaps but usually it
등등 그래서이 작업은 아마도하지만 보통을 약간 더 비싸다
completely washes away
완전히 씻어
compared to everything else you're worried about which is all the
당신이하는 걱정 다른 모든 것들에 비해 모든입니다
competitions over the image of God
하나님의 형상을 통해 대회
probably
아마도
exact same problem and so maximizing the property and maximizing the locality
동일한 문제 등 특성을 극대화하고 지역을 극대화
give you the identical result but in terms of the match everything comes out
경기의 모든 나오는 당신에게 동일한 결과 있지만 측면에서 제공
too much nicer looking when you actually put a lot of there but it's the exact
너무 멋진 당신이 실제로이 많이 넣으면 찾고 있지만 정확한이다
same optimization problem
동일한 최적화 문제
ok let's get some interpretations of these two and exactly how they differ
확인의 그들이 차이가 정확히 어떻게 이러한 둘의 해석을 얻을 수 있습니다
max vs SEM and trying to give you an idea about one property that actually
SEM 대 최대 당신에게 아이디어를 제공하기 위해 노력에 대한 하나의 속성 실제로
quite different between the two
둘 사이의 상당히 다른
these two different functional analysis team that we have these three examples
우리가이 세 가지 예를 다음 두 가지 기능 분석 팀
all three examples and suppose there are three closest three different examples
세 가지 예제와 세 가까운 세 가지 예제가있는 가정
and these are discourse of these examples for every one of these examples
이들은 이러한 예제 하나 하나에 대한이 예제의 담론이다
the first class here is the correct class so 10 is the correct class score
여기에 첫 번째 클래스는 올바른 클래스 그래서 10이 올바른 수준의 점수입니다
and the other scores are these guys either the first one second or third one
다른 점수는이 사람들 중 첫 번째 두 번째 또는 세 번째는
and now just think about how would these losses tell you about how desirable
지금은 단지 이러한 손실이 얼마나 바람직한에 대해 얘기하는 방법을 생각
outcomes are in terms of that w in particular one way to think about it for
결과는 그것에 대해 생각하는 특정 하나의 방법으로 승 그 측면에
example is suppose I think this data point the third one tenth of a hundred
예를 들어 내가이 데이터는 백의 세 번째 십분의 일을 가리키는 생각한다고 가정한다
and eight hundred and suppose I jiggle it move it around a bit and my input
그리고 팔백 내가 조금 내 입력 주위를 이동 가볍게 흔들다 가정
space what is happening to the losses as I do that
내가 그렇게 같은 공간 손실에 무슨 일이 일어나고
I do so they increase and decrease as I would go around do they both increase or
나는 그들이 둘 다 증가 할들이 증가 및 감소 내가 주위에 이동하는 것처럼 그렇게 나
decrease for the third appointment for example as me and remains the same
나 예를 들어 제 약속 줄이고 동일하게 유지
correct and why is that it's because the margin was met by a huge amount so
정확한 이유는 마진이 그렇게 엄청난 금액으로 이어졌습니다 때문에이 점이다
there's just added robustness when I take the day off on a sheet around the
나는 주위의 시트에 하루를 찍을 때 그냥 견고성이 추가됩니다
SVM is already very happy because the margins were met by you know we desire
우리가 원하는 알고에 의해 여백이 충족 되었기 때문에 SVM은 이미 매우 행복하다
margin of one and here we have a margin of two hundred and there's a huge margin
여기에 하나의 마진 우리는 이백의 여유를 가지고 거대한 여백이있다
ESPN doesn't express a preference over these examples where this course come
이 과정이 올 곳 ESPN은 이러한 예를 통해 환경 설정을 표현하지 않습니다
out very negative ads no additional preference over do I want to be negative
이상 내가 부정되고 싶어하지 않는다 추가 환경 설정 매우 부정적인 광고 아웃
2009 200,000 PSP and wound care but the s but the South max could always see you
2009 200,000 PSP 및 상처 치료 만의 그러나 남부 최대 수 항상 당신을보고
will always get an improvement for something that's right so soft max
항상 옳다 그래서 소프트 맥스가 뭔가에 대한 개선을 얻을 것이다
function express a preference for everyone's needs to be negative about
기능에 대해 부정적인 것으로 모든 사람의 요구에 대한 선호를 표현
two hundred or five hundred or thousand of them will give you better loss right
이백이나 오백 또는 이들의 천명은 더 나은 손실 권리를 줄 것이다
but the SVM at this point doesn't care if the other examples I don't know if
다른 예는 내가 알고하지 않으면하지만이 시점에서 SVM은 상관하지 않는다
it's as clear distinction rights of the FBI has decided robustness to it once
연방 수사 국 (FBI)의 명확한 구분이 권한을 한 번에 견고성을 결정했다대로입니다
this margin to be met but beyond that it doesn't micromanage your course where
이 마진이 충족되어야합니다하지만 그 이상은 코스 어디 세세한하지 않습니다
soft max will always want peace course to be you know everything here nothing
소프트 맥스는 항상 당신이 모든 것을 아무것도 알 수 평화 과정을 원할 것입니다
there and so that's one kind of very clear difference between the two
그래서 둘 사이의 차이가 명확 1 종 존재하고있어
it was a question
이 질문했다
yes the margin of one I mentioned very briefly that that's not a hyper primary
예 하나의 이익률은 그게 하이퍼 차 아니다 매우 간략하게 언급
you can fix it to be one reason for that is that lease course they're the kind of
즉 그리스 코스입니다 당신은의 친절 하나의 이유가 고칠 수
the absolute values of those course are kind of don't really mattered because my
그 과정의 절대 값을 가지 정말 때문에 중요하지 않습니다되어 내
W I can make it a larger or smaller and I can achieve different sizes course and
WI 그것이 더 크거나 작게 만들 수 있고, 내가 다른 크기의 과정을 달성 할 수 있으며,
so one turns out to work better and in the notes I have a longer duration go
그래서 하나는 잘 작동 밝혀과 노트에 나는 더 긴 기간이 갈이
into details exactly why one is safe to choose so refer to that but i dont wanna
세부 사항을 정확히 이유 하나 때문에 선택이 참조하는 것이 안전하지만 난 싶지 해달라고
spend time on it in like 20 would be if you wanna 20 there would be trouble you
당신이 20 싶어하는 경우 문제가있을 것 같은 20에서 시간을 보내고는 것
can use any positive number and that would give you a nice p.m. if he was 0
양수를 사용할 수 있습니다 그가 0 인 경우 그것은 당신에게 좋은 오후를 줄 것이다
that would look different
그 다르게 보일 것입니다
for example this added constant there one property gives you when you actually
예를 들어이 경우 실제로 하나의 속성을 제공가 일정 추가
go through the mathematical analysis likes in the ass p.m. in CST 29 as
CST (29)의 엉덩이 오후의 수학적 분석의 좋아하는을 통해로 이동
you'll see that the chief suspects margin property where the Eskimo playing
최고는 에스키모 재생 여백 속성을 의심 것을 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
that the best margin when you actually have a plus
최고의 마진 실제로 플러스을 때
constant their combined with the altar regularization on the way it's very
상수는 길에 제단 정규화와 결합 된 아주의 자신의
small weights that meet specific margin and as well give you this very nice mix
특정 마진을 충족뿐만 아니라 당신이 아주 좋은 혼합을 제공 작은 무게
margin property that I didn't really going to in this in this lecture right
난 정말이 강의에서이에서로 이동하지 않은 여백 재산권
now but I basically do want a positive number there otherwise things would
지금 그러나 나는 기본적 그렇지 않으면이 양수를 일을 할 싶어
break
단절
numbers that are real numbers and we're kind of free to get in this course out
실수하고 우리는 종류의 무료 아웃이 과정에서 얻을 수있는 좋은 방법입니다 번호
and it's up to you to endow them with interpretation right we can have
바로 우리가 수 있으며 해석을 부여하도록 당신의
different losses in this specific case I showed you the closest p.m. there's
거기에이 특정한 경우에 다른 손실은 내가 당신에게 가장 가까운시를 보였다
multiple versions of a multi-class SVM you can paddle around with exactly the
멀티 클래스 SVM의 여러 버전은 정확히 주위에 헤엄 수 있습니다
Los expression in one of the one of the interpretations we can put on this
우리는이에 넣을 수있는 해석의 하나 일 로스 식
course then there'd be some normalized block probably say they can't be
코스는 아마도 그들이 할 수없는 말을 몇 가지 표준화 된 블록이있을 것
normalized because they just came we have to explicitly because there's no
그들은 단지 온 정규화 때문에 우리는 더이 있기 때문에 명시 적으로해야
constraint that the output of your function will be normalized and they
함수의 출력이 정상화 될 것이라고 제약 조건과 그들이
have to be the camp probably because you're out that in just his real numbers
당신은 단지 자신의 실수에 그 밖으로이기 때문에 아마 캠프를해야
that can be positive or negative so we interpret them as a problem peace and
즉 양 또는 음이 될 수 있도록 우리가 문제를 평화로를 해석하고
and done
및 수행
requires us to treat them some very bad kind of explanation of it but I think
우리를 필요로하는 것은 그들에게 그것을 설명 매우 나쁜 종류를 취급하지만 난 생각하는
he's got
그는 있어요
energy and losses like kind of an equivalent of all about what you're
에너지와 당신이있어 무엇에 대한 모든 동등한 종류의 같은 손실
saying look at this one here right here saying if I googled this around
나는 주위에이를 봤 경우 말을 여기 여기 하나 봐 말
nothing's changing I think the difference is the loss would definitely
아무것도 나는 차이가 확실히 손실 것이라고 생각 변화없는 것
change for max even though it wouldn't change a lot but I would definitely
가 많이 변경하지 않을 경우에도 최대에 대한 변경하지만 난 확실히 것
change the subject to express preference whereas p.m. guess you identically zero
환경 설정을 표현하는 제목을 변경 오후 반면 당신이 동일 제로 같아요
wouldn't be very big blunder differently as preference but in practice basically
다른 선호도하지만, 기본적으로 실제로는 매우 큰 실수를하지 않을 것이다
this distinction the interaction of trying to give you is that the SPM has a
이 구별 당신에게 노력의 상호 작용은 SPM이있다이다
very local part of the space immature classifying that it cares about and
공간의 매우 로컬 부분이 관심이 있다고 분류 미숙에 대한과
beyond it
그 이후
its environment and a soft max kind of physical action of the full data cloud
환경 및 전체 데이터 구름 물리적 작용 소프트 맥스 종류
it cares about it cares about all the points in your data cloud not just you
그것은 당신의 데이터를 클라우드에 대한 모든 사항을 관심에 대해 그냥 당신을하지 관심
know there's like a small class here that you're trying to separate out from
당신으로부터 분리하려는 것은 여기에서 작은 클래스처럼 거기에 알고
everything else
다른 모든 것들
assault Maxwell kind of concerned the full data closet getting your plane and
해당 전체 데이터 옷장의 공격 맥스웰 종류의 비행기를 얻고
SPM just want to separate out that tiny piece from the immediate part of the
SPM 단지의 직접적인 부분에서 작은 조각 것을 구분합니다
data cloud like that in practice when you actually run the state can give
실제로 같은 데이터 구름이 실제로 국가가 제공 할 수 있습니다 실행할 때
nearly identical results almost always so really when trying to I'm not trying
내가 노력 아니에요에 거의 동일한 결과는 거의 항상 정말하려고 할 때
to pitch one or the other I'm just trying to give you this notion that
하나의 피치하거나 그냥 시도하고 다른 하나는 당신이 개념을주고 그
you're in charge of the loss function you get some scores out and you can
당신은 당신이 밖으로 약간의 점수를 얻을 손실 기능을 담당하고있어, 당신은 할 수
write down nearly any mathematical expression
거의 모든 수식을 적어
is differentiable into what you want your scores to be like and there are
당신이 당신의 점수처럼되고 싶은에 미분하고있다
different ways of actually formulating this and actually two examples that are
다른 사실이 수립의 방법과입니다 실제로 두 가지 예
coming to see practice but in practice we can put down any losses for what you
연습을보기 위해 오는 그러나 실제로 우리는 무엇을 어떤 손실을 넣을 수 있습니다
want your scores to be and that's a very nice picture because we can optimize
점수이 원하는 우리가 최적화 할 수 있기 때문에 그것은 아주 좋은 사진입니다
overall let me show you an interactive web them at this point
전반적인 날이 시점에서 당신에게 대화 형 웹을 보여 드리겠습니다
alright see this so this is an interactive seminar class page you can
이것은 당신이 할 수있는 대화 형 세미나 클래스 페이지가 그래서 확실히이 참조
find it at this URL I wrote it last year and I have to show it to all of you guys
이 URL에서 찾을 작년를 쓴 나는 너희들 모두에게 보여해야
to justify spending one day on developing ok but some that your last
확인 개발에 지출 하루 정당화하지만, 일부 그 마지막을합니다
year not too many people looked at this vehicle is one day of my life so we have
올해 너무 많은 사람들이 차량에서 발견하지 그래서 우리는 내 삶의 하루가있다
here is a two-dimensional problem with three classes and I'm showing here three
여기에 세 가지 클래스와 이차원 문제는 내가 여기에 세 가지를 보여주는거야
classes each has three examples over here in two dimensions and I'm showing
클래스 각각은 여기에 두 개의 차원을 통해 세 가지 예를 가지고 있는데 보여주는거야
the three classifiers here because the level set aside for example the red
여기에 세 가지 분류는 수준은 예를 빨간색 방치하기 때문에
classifier is as scores of 0 along the line and then I'm showing the arrows
분류는 선을 따라 0의 점수로하고 그때의 화살표를 보여주는거야
which scores increased right here's RW matrix so as you recall the W matrix
이는 당신이 W 매트릭스 기억으로, 그래서 여기 증가 점수 RW 행렬이다
double rows of that w matrix are the different classifiers so we have the
우리는이 그래서 w 행렬의 두 행은 서로 다른 분류입니다
blue classifier red and green classifier and Brett classifier and we have both
파란색 분류 빨간색과 녹색의 분류와 브렛 분류 및 우리가 모두
the weights for both the X&Y component and also the bias and then here we have
여기에 우리가 다음 X & Y 구성 요소 또한 바이어스 모두에 대한 가중치
the data said so we have the X&Y coordinates of all the data points there
데이터는 우리가 모든 데이터 포인트의 X 및 Y 좌표를 상기 그래서
correct label and thus course as well as the loss achieved by all those data
올바른 라벨 따라서 과정뿐만 아니라 모든 데이터에 의해 달성 손실
points right now with this setting up w and so you can see that I'm taking the
이 w 설정하고 그래서 내가 데려 갈거야 것을 볼 수 있습니다로 지금 포인트
mean overall the loss so right now our data losses 2.77 regularization loss for
우리의 데이터 손실이 너무 좋아 지금은 2.77 정규화 손실이 전체 손실을 의미
this w is 3.5 and talk hola 6.27
이 w 3.5과 이야기 안녕 6.27이다
and so basically you can fiddle around with this so so as I change my W you can
그래서 기본적으로 내가 내 W를 변경할 수 있도록 그래서 당신이 할 수있는이 주위에 바이올린 수 있습니다
see that here I'm making my W one of the WC bigger and you can see what that does
내 W 더 큰 WC 중 하나 만들고있어 여기에 볼 당신은 그 무엇을 볼 수 있습니다
in in their order bias you can see the bias basically shut these high plains
순서 바이어스에서 당신은 바이어스는 기본적으로 이러한 높은 평야를 종료 볼 수 있습니다
okay and then what we can do is we can we're going to work this kind of a
우리가 할 수있는 일 후 좋아하고 우리는 우리가 이런 종류의 작업을 진행하고 있습니다입니다
preview of what's going to happen we're getting the loss here and there were
무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지의 미리보기 우리가 여기 손실을 얻고 일어나고 있었다하기
going to do back propagation which has given us the gradient over how we want
전파를 다시하기 위하여려고하는 것은 우리에게 우리가 원하는 방법을 통해 기울기를 부여하고있다있는
to adjust these W it's in order to make the law smaller and so we're going to do
이 법이 작고 만들기 위해의 W 이러한 조정 그래서 우리는 할거야
is this repeated states where we start off with this w but now I can improve I
이것은 우리가이 w로 시작 상태를 반복한다하지만 지금 난을 향상시킬 수 있습니다
can improve this set of W's so when I do a perimeter update this is actually
W의이 세트를 향상 그래서 주변 업데이트를 수행 할 때이 실제로 수
using these gradients which are shown here in the right now and it's actually
지금 바로 여기에 표시됩니다 이러한 그라디언트를 사용하여 실제로입니다
making a tiny changed everything
작은 변화 모두를 만들기
according to this gradient right so as I do
바로 그래서 내가 할로이 경사에 따라
primary update you can see that the loss here is decreasing special the total
차 업데이트는 여기 손실이 총 특별한 감소하고 있음을 알 수
loss here so the lost just keeps getting better and better as I do primary date
여기 손실 잃어버린 내가 할로 단지 더 좋아 계속 차 날짜 때문에
so this is the process of optimization that we're going to go into in a bit so
그래서 이것은 우리가 조금에 들어갈거야 최적화의 과정이다
I can also start a repeated update and then basically we keep improving this w
또한 반복되는 업데이트를 시작하고 기본적으로 우리는이 w를 개선 유지
over and over until our loss it started off was roughly three or something that
이상 우리의 손실 때까지 진형을 통해 대략 세 또는 무언가였습니다
you are mean loss over the data is point one like that and we're correctly
당신은 데이터에 대한 평균 손실은 같은 하나의 포인트입니다 그리고 우리가 제대로이야
classifying all these buttons here so I can also randomized randomized W so just
나는 또한 그래서 그냥 (W) 무작위 랜덤 수 있도록 여기에 모든 버튼을 분류
kind of knocks it off and then there's always converges these acting point
종류의 그것을 노크하고 거기에 항상 이러한 행동 포인트를 수렴
through the process optimization and you can play here with the regularization as
공정 최적화를 통해 당신은 정규화으로 여기 재생할 수 있습니다
well you have different forms of loss so the one I shown you right now is there
하나는 내가 지금 당신을 보여 있도록 잘 손실의 다른 형태가되어 있습니다
was a consensus p.m. formulation there's a few more SPM formulations and there's
합의 오후 제제는 몇 가지 더 SPM 제제가 그리고 거기에 있었다
also soft max here you'll see that when I Swisher soft max loss our losses look
또한 여기에 소프트 맥스는 내가 우리의 손실이 스위셔 소프트 최대 손실을 볼 때 것을 볼 수 있습니다
different and but the solution and are being roughly the same so when I switch
다른하고 있지만 솔루션은 I 스위치 그렇게 할 때 거의 같은되고있다
back to him you know the type of players move around the tiny bit but really it's
다시 그에게 당신은 작은 조각 주위에 이동 플레이어의 유형을 알고 있지만 정말이야
it's mostly the same and so this is just a size so this is how much how big steps
그것은 대부분 동일합니다이 얼마나 얼마나 큰 단계 그래서 그래서 이것은 단지 크기
are we making when we get the gradient on how to improve things so much promise
우리는 너무 많은 약속 일을 개선하는 방법에 그라데이션을 얻을 때 우리는하고 있습니다
we should start with the very biggest upside the scenes are giggling trying to
우리는 장면이 킥킥 웃고하려고하는 매우 큰 상승을 시작한다
separate out these data points and then over time we're going to be doing in a
이러한 데이터 포인트를 분리 한 후 시간이 지남에 따라 우리는에서 일을 할거야
position as we're going to decrease our updates eyes and this thing or just
우리가 우리의 업데이 트의 눈을 감소거야로 위치와이 일을하거나
slowly converging on the premise that we want in the end and so so you can play
천천히 우리는 결국 원하는 그래서 그래서 당신은 재생할 수있는 전제 수렴
with us and you can see how he scores to go around and what the losses and if I
우리와 함께 당신은 그가 점수는 손실이 나는 경우를 주위에 가서 어떤 방법을 볼 수 있습니다
stop repeated update you can also drag these points but I think on the Mac it
당신이 이러한 점을 드래그 할 수 있습니다 반복 갱신을 중지하지만 맥 그것을 생각
doesn't work so I tried to drag this point it disappears so good
내가 그렇게 좋은 사라이 점을 드래그하려고 그렇게 작동하지 않습니다
but it works on a desktop so I don't go in and figure out exactly what happened
하지만 바탕 화면에서 작동 그래서 내가 가서 무슨 일이 있었 정확히 파악하지
there but they can play with this
그러나이 거기 재생할 수 있습니다
we have as mean loss over data plus regularization this is one other diagram
우리는 이것이 다른 한 도면이다 데이터 플러스 정규화 이상으로 평균 손실이
to show you how did what this looks like I don't think it's a very good diagram
나는 그것이 아주 좋은도 생각하지 않습니다처럼이 어떻게 생겼는지 한 방법을 보여
and there's something confusing about it that I can't remember from last year but
내가 작년 기억할 수없는 그것에 대해 혼란 거기에 뭔가하지만,
basically you have this data and why your images your labels and there's W
기본적으로이 데이터가 왜 이미지 레이블 및 W있다
and keeping this course and getting the lawsuit and the regularization losses
이 과정을 유지하고 소송을 얻고 정규화 손실
only function of the weights not of the data and mister what we want to do now
우리가 지금 무엇을 원하는가 아닌 데이터와 아저씨의 무게의 기능
is we don't have control over the data set right that's given to us we have
우리는 우리에게 주어진 것 바로 데이터 세트 우리가 제어 할 수없는된다
control over that w and as we changed at W the loss will be different so for any
그 w를 제어하고 우리가 손실 W 변경할로 다를 수 있습니다 어떤을 위해 그렇게
W give me I can compute the loss and that lost is linked to how well we're
W 내가 손실을 계산할 수 나를 포기하고 그 손실은 우리가있어 얼마나 잘 연결되어 있습니다
classifying all of our examples so one thing a low loss means world-class find
우리의 모든 예제를 분류하는 것은 낮은 손실은 세계 최고 수준의 발견을 의미 한 가지도록
them very very well on the training data and then we're crossing our fingers that
그들을 아주 잘의 훈련 데이터, 그리고, 우리는 우리의 손가락이 교차하고
also works on some test data that we haven't seen so here's one strategy for
또한 우리가 여기 보지 못했다 테스트 데이터에서 작동하는 하나의 전략이다
optimization it's a random search so because we can evaluate loss for any
우리가 어떤에 대한 손실을 평가할 수 있기 때문에 있도록 최적화는 임의의 검색입니다
arbitrary W when I can afford to do and I'm not sure if i dont im go through
임의 W는 때 나는 어떻게 감당할 수와 내가 메신저를 통해 이동 해달라고 있는지 확실하지 않습니다
this in full detail but effectively I randomly sampled and I can check their
이 전체 상세히하지만 효과적으로 나는 무작위로 샘플링 나는 확인할 수 있습니다 자신의
loss and I can just keep track of the W that works best
손실 난 그냥 가장 적합한 W 추적 할 수 있습니다
oK so that's an amazing process of optimization of getting check and it
좋아, 그래서 점점 점검과 최적화의 놀라운 과정이다
turns out if you do this I think I tried two thousand times if you do this
이 작업을 수행 할 경우, 나는이 작업을 수행 할 경우 내가 이천 번 시도 생각 밝혀
thousand times and take the best W found at random and you run it on your seat
천 번과 최고의 W는 무작위로 발견 걸릴 당신은 당신의 좌석에서 실행
bartend data just made up you end up with about 15.5 percent accuracy and
당신이 약 15.5 %의 정확도로 결국 그냥 만든 데이터를 바텐더와
since they're acting classes are the mean baseline as a 10% chance
그들이 행동하고 있기 때문에 클래스는 10 %의 확률로 평균 기준은
performance so 15.5 there some signal actually notably and so state of the art
성능 때문에 15.5이 실제로 특히와 예술의 매우 상태 일부 신호
is that ninety-five which is a common that so we have some got too close over
아흔다섯 공통입니다 그래서 우리는 몇 가지를 통해 너무 가까이 가지고 있다는 점이다
the next
다음
two weeks or so so this is so don't use this just because it's on the slides one
이 슬라이드 하나에 그냥 있기 때문에 2 주 정도 그래서 이것은 그래서이를 사용하지 않는있다
interpretation of exactly what this looks like this process optimization is
이 프로세스 최적화처럼 정확히 어떤이의 해석은 보인다
that we have this loss landscape right this loss landscape is in this high
우리가이 손실 풍경을 가지고 바로이 손실 풍경이 높은에
dimensional W space so here we sit here in 3d and your losses the height then
우리는 그 다음 차원에서 앉아서 당신의 손실 높이 여기도록 차원 W 공간
you only have 2 W's in this case and you're here and you're blindfolded W you
당신은 단지 2 W의이 경우가 있고 당신은 여기 그리고 당신 (W) 눈을 가리고있어
can see where the valleys are but you're trying to find low loss as you're
계곡이 있지만 당신은 당신이있는 한 낮은 손실을 찾기 위해 노력하고 위치를 볼 수 있습니다
blindfolded and you have an altitude meter and so you can tell what your
눈을 가린 당신은 고도 측정기를 가지고 있고 그래서 당신은 무엇을 말할 수 있습니다
losses at any single point and you're trying to get to the bottom of the
단일 지점에서의 손실과 당신의 하단에 도착하기 위해 노력하고
valley right and so that's really the process of optimization and what we've
계곡 오른쪽 그래서 정말 최적화하는 과정이고 우리가했습니다
shown you would actually so far as this random optimization where you teleport
당신은 것 도시 실제로 지금까지 당신이 순간 이동이 임의의 최적화로
around and you just check your altitude right so not the best idea so we're
주위에 당신은 단지 우리가있어 너무 좋아 너무 좋은 생각을 당신의 고도를하지 확인
going to do instead is we're going to use what I refer to as a gradient or
우리가 그라데이션으로 내가 참조 무​​엇을 사용하려고하고있다 대신 할 예정이나
really we're just computing the slope across in every single direction so I'm
정말 우리가 너무 난 모든 단일 방향으로 가로 질러 기울기를 계산하고
trying to compute the slope and then I'm going to go downhill ok so we're
기울기를 계산하기 위해 노력하고 우리가있어 그래서 내리막 확인 갈거야
following the slope I'm not going to go into too much detail on this but
나는이 있지만, 너무 많은 세부 사항으로 갈 않을거야 기울기를 다음
basically there's an expression for the gradient which is defined like that
기본적으로 그렇게 정의 된 그라데이션 표현이있다
there's a derivative populist 101 definition and multiple dimensions if
파생 포퓰리즘 (101) 정의와 여러 차원 경우가있다
you have a director of derivatives that's referred to as the gradient right
당신은 그라데이션 권리라고있어 파생 상품의 이사가
so because we have multiple dimensions multiple w's we have a gradient vector
우리의 승 여러 차원을 여러가 그렇게 때문에 우리는 그라데이션 벡터가
ok so this is the expression and in fact we can numerically evaluate the
확인 그래서 이것은 표현이며, 실제로 우리는 수치를 평가할 수 있습니다
expression before I go into the Analects how to show you what that would look
식 그게 보일 것 무엇을 표시하는 방법 논어에 가기 전에
like to evaluate the gradient at some W suppose we have some current W and we're
일부 W의 그라데이션 우리는 약간의 현재 W를 가지고 우리가있어 가정 평가하려면
getting some loss ok what we want to do not want to get an idea about the slope
우리는 경사에 대한 아이디어를 얻을 싶지 않아하고 싶은 일부 손실이 좋아지고
at this point so we're going to basically look at this formula and we're
그래서이 시점에서 우리는 기본적으로이 공식에서 볼거야 그리고 우리는있어
just going to evaluated so I'm going to go in the first dimension and I'm going
그냥 첫 번째 차원에 갈거야 그래서 평가에 가서 내가 갈거야
and really what this is telling you to do is evaluate explosive your altitude
정말 어떻게이 수행 할 수 말하고있는 것은 폭발 고도를 평가입니다
at Xmas H subtracted from FFX and divide by H
크리스마스 H에 H에 의해 FFX 및 분할에서 제외
what that response to as me being on this landscape taking a small step in
어떤 날의 작은 단계를 복용이 풍경 것으로 해당 응답
some direction and looking whether or not my foot went up or down
어떤 방향으로할지 여부를보고 내 발은 올라 갔다 아래로
right that's what the gradient is telling me so I took a small step and
바로 그 때문에 나는 작은 단계를 데리고 어떤 기울기가 말해가요
the lost there is 1.25 then I can use that formula with a finite difference
잃어버린 1.25 그때 유한 차이가 그 공식을 사용할 수있다
approximation we review the small H two actually derived that the gradient here
근사 우리는 작은 H이 실제로 파생 검토가 여기에 그라데이션
as negative 2.5 the slope downwards so I took a step the loss and decreased so
마이너스 2.5로 기울기는 아래로 그래서 나는 단계에게 손실을 가져다가 이렇게 감소
the sloping downwards in terms of the loss function so negative 2.5 in that
점에서 손실 함수의 관점 그래서 마이너스 2.5 하향 경
particular dimension so I can do this for every single dimension independently
특히 치수는 그래서 독립적으로 모든 단일 차원에 대해이 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다
right so I go into the second dimension I add a small amount so I step in a
나는에 단계 그래서 바로 그래서 내가 작은 금액을 추가 두 번째 차원으로 이동
different direction I look at what happened to the loss I use that formula
나는 손실에 무슨 일이 있었는지를 보면 다른 방향 나는 공식 것을 사용
and is telling me that the gradient the slope is 2.6 I can do that in the third
및 기울기가 2.6 인 그라데이션 내가 세 번째에 해당 할 수 있다고 말해됩니다
dimension and I get the grieving ok so what I'm referring to here is basically
기본적으로 내가 여기서 말하는 겁니다 치수와 나는 확인 너무 슬퍼하세요
evaluating the numerical ingredient which is using the spine a difference
척추의 차를 사용하는 성분 수치를 평가
approximation where for every single dimension independently I can take a
모든 단일 차원에 대해 독립적으로 내가 걸릴 수 있습니다 근사
small step at the loss and that tells me the slower is it going upwards or
작은 손실에 단계 그리고 나에게 느린 지시가 위쪽으로 갈거나
downwards for every single one of these parameters and so this is America
아래 이러한 매개 변수의 모든 하나 하나 등이 미국이다
gradient the way this would look like it is by con funk shun here it looks ugly
그것은 추한 보이는 여기를 피하는이 그것과 같을 것이다 방법을 사기 펑크가된다 그라데이션
because it turns out it's slightly tricky to iterate over all the W's but
그것이 나오는 것에 있기 때문에 반복 약간 까다로운 모든 W의 만
basically we're just looking at age comparing two effects and dividing by
기본적으로 우리는 단지 두 가지 효과를 비교로 나누어 나이에 찾고
age and we're getting agreement now the problem with this is if you want to use
우리가 계약을 받고있어 나이 사용할 경우 지금의 문제입니다
the numerical gradient event of course we have to do this for every single
물론 수치 그라데이션 이벤트는 우리가 매일이 작업을 수행해야
dimension to get a sense of what the great iam this endeavor single dimension
차원은 어떤 위대한 스피 이러한 노력 단일 차원의 감각을 얻을 수
and right when you have a comment you have hundreds of millions of parameters
당신은 코멘트를 때 오른쪽 당신은 매개 변수의 수백만의 수백
right so we can't afford to actually check the loss in hundreds of millions
바로 그래서 우리는 실제로 수억의 손실을 확인 할 여유가 없다
of primaries before we do a single step so this approach where we would try to
예비 선거의 우리는 한 단계 우리가하려고 것 때문에이 방법을하기 전에
evaluate the gradient numerically is approximate because we're using finite
우리는 유한 사용하고 있기 때문에 평가 그라데이션 수치 대략적인
difference approximation second is also extremely slow because I need to do
내가 할 필요가 있기 때문에 차분 근사 둘째도 매우 느립니다
million checks on the loss function on the icon that before I know what the
아이콘의 손실 함수에 만 확인 내가 무엇을 알기도 전에 것이
gradient doesn't I can take a primary update so very slow approximate turns
그라데이션 나는 매우 느린 대략적인 회전 수 있도록 차 업데이트를 취할 수 없습니다
out that this is all so silly right because the loss as a function of W as
이 때문에 바보 권리는 모든 것을 밖으로 때문에 W의 함수로 손실
we've written about it and really what we want is we want the gradient of the
우리는 그것에 대해 서면으로 작성했습니다 정말 우리가 원하는 것을 우리는의 기울기를 원하는됩니다
last 11 respectively and luckily we can just write that down
각각 11 마지막 운 좋게 우리는 단지를 쓸 수 있습니다
thanks to these guys actually know who those guys are doing that's right you
이 녀석 덕분에 실제로 당신이 바로 그 사람이하고있는 사람을 알고
know which is which could just get a look remarkably similar but basically
단지 모양이 매우 비슷하지만, 기본적으로 얻을 수있는 것입니다 알고
anything like this to inventors of calculus there's actually controversy
미적분학의 발명자에 이런 일이 실제로 논란이있다
over who really invented calculus and these guys each other over it but
이상 사람 정말 발명 한 미적분시키고이 사람이 서로를하지만,
basically calculus is this powerful hammer and so what we can do is instead
기본적으로 수학이 강력한 망치이며, 우리가 할 수있는 일이 아닌 것입니다
of doing the silly thing we're evaluating numerical gradient we can
어리석은 일을의 우리는 우리가 할 수있는 수치 그라데이션을 평가하고
actually use calculus and we can break down an expression for what the gradient
실제로 수학을 사용하고 우리는 어떤 기울기에 대한 표현을 분해 할 수 있습니다
is off the loss function in the white space so basically instead of fumbling
공백의 손실 함수 떨어져 그래서 기본적으로 대신 멍청이
around and doing this is it going up or is it going down by checking the loss I
주변이 작업은 최대 것입니다 아니면 손실 I을 선택하여 추락
just have an expression where I take the gradient of this and I can sync simply
그냥이의 그라데이션을 표현을하고 난 간단하게 동기화 할 수 있습니다
evaluate what the entire matter is that the only way that you can actually run
전체 물질이 실제로있는 유일한 방법을 실행할 수 있다는 것입니다 무엇 평가
this in practice right we can just an expression for years the gradient we can
년 동안이 연습의 권리를 우리는 할 수 있습니다 만 표현 우리가 할 수있는 그라데이션
do to stop and so on so in summary basically numerical gradient approximate
그래서 중지하려면 어떻게 요약 기본적으로 숫자 그라데이션 대략에게에 너무
slow but very easy to write because you're just doing this very simple
느리지 만 그냥이 매우 간단한 일을하고 있기 때문에 쓰기 아주 쉽게
process for any damage or loss function I can get the gradient vector for a
손해 나 손실에 기능에 대한 처리 난에 대한 그라데이션 벡터를 얻을 수 있습니다
gradient which is you actually do calculus its exact no finite
당신이 실제로 할 것입니다 구배는 정확한에는 유한을 수학하지
proclamations it's very fast but it's error-prone because you actually have to
포고문 매우 빨리하지만 오류가 발생하기 쉬운 당신이 실제로에 있기 때문이다
do math right so in practice what you see is we always use a lot of gradient
실제로 바로 그래서 수학을 당신이 무엇을보고 우리는 항상 그라데이션을 많이 사용
we do calculus we figure out what the gradient should be but then you always
우리는 항상 우리가 그라데이션해야 알아낼 수학을하지만,
check your implementation using an American gradient check as its referred
그것의 언급으로 미국의 그라데이션 체크를 사용하여 구현을 확인
to so I will do all I care about the loss function should be I write an
그래서 나는 내가 작성해야합니다 나는 손실 함수에 대한 관심을 모두 수행 할 수 있습니다
expression for the gradient I evaluated in my code so I get in the holiday
내 코드에서 평가 된 그라데이션 표현은 그래서 휴가를 얻을
greetings and then I also have a lead in numerical gradient on the side and that
인사는 다음 나는 또한 측면에와 있음을 수치 그라데이션의 리드가
takes a while but you mature you have a lead to more convenient and you make
잠시 필요하지만 당신은 당신에게 더 편리 리드가 성숙하면 확인
sure that those two are the same and then we say that you passed the green
그 두 가지가 동일하고 우리는 당신이 녹색을 통과라고 확인
truck oK so that's what you see in practice whenever you try to develop a
그래서 트럭 확인 당신이 개발을 시도 할 때마다 당신이 실제로 무엇을보고있어
new module for internal network you're right I would have lost your right to
내부 네트워크에 대한 새로운 모듈은 바로 내가 할 수있는 권리를 잃은 것하고
backward pass for a complete the gradient and then you have to make sure
당신이 확인해야 다음 그라데이션 완전하고 대한 후방 패스
the gradient check it just to make sure that your calculus is correct and then I
그라데이션은 당신의 수학이 정확한지 확인해 확인하고 I
already referred to this process of optimization which we saw nicely in the
이미 우리는에 잘 보았다 최적화이 과정 함
Web Demo where we have this
우리가이 웹 데모
loop when we optimized where we simply Valley the gradient on your loss
루프는 우리는 당신의 손실에 어디서 단순히 밸리 그라데이션을 최적화 할 때
function and then knowing the gradient we can perform a primer update when we
때 그라데이션을 아는 기능, 그리고, 우리는 프라이머 업데이트를 수행 할 수 있습니다
change the WBI tiny amount in particular we want to update with the negative
우리가 부정적으로 업데이트 할 특히 WBI 작은 양을 변경할
step-size times the gradient the negative is there because the gradient
스텝 사이즈 배 네거티브 기울기 때문에 존재 그래디언트
tells the direction of the greatest increase it tells you which way the
그것은 당신을 알려줍니다 가장 큰 증가의 방향을 알려줍니다 끝까지
losses increasing and want to minimize it which is where the negative it's
손실이 증가하고 부정적인 그것은 어디 인을 최소화하려면
coming from where to go and negative reading direction step size here as a
어디에서 오는 가서 여기에 음의 판독 방향 스텝 크기로
hyper primary that will cause you a huge amount of headaches step size are
당신에게있는 두통의 스텝 크기의 거대한 양의가 발생할 하이퍼 차
learning rate this is the most critical parameter to basically worry about that
비율이 기본적으로 걱정하는 가장 중요한 매개 변수입니다 학습
really there's two that you have to worry about the most the step size or
정말 당신은 스텝 크기 또는 대부분에 대해 걱정할 필요가 두 개의있다
learning rate and there's the regularization strength lame duck that
속도를 학습하고 정규화 강도 레임덕이있다 그
we saw already those two parameters are really the two largest headaches and
우리가 이미 보았던 그 두 개의 매개 변수 정말이 가장 큰 두통이며,
that's usually what we cross body Dover was a question about but it's not that
그것은 우리가 몸 도버에 대한 질문이었다 교차 무엇 일반적이다하지만 그 아니다
great just great and it tells you the slope in every single direction and then
큰 단지 위대하고 그것은 당신에게 경사 매 방향으로 다음을 알려줍니다
we just take a step by step it so the process of opposition in the weight
우리는 단지 단계 그래서 무게에 반대의 과정에 의한 조치를 취할
space is your somewhere in your W you get your gradient any March some amount
공간은 W에 어딘가에 당신이 당신의 그라데이션 어떠한 월 일부 금액을 얻을 수있다
in the direction of the gradient but you don't know how much so that the step
그러나 그라디언트의 방향으로 당신은 얼마나 알고하지 않도록하는 단계
size and you saw that when I increase the step size in the demo things were
크기와 내가 데모 일에 스텝 크기를 증가시 더라
jubilant generating around quite a lot right there was a lot of energy no
꽤 많은 주위에 기뻐 생성 바로 에너지없이 많이 있었다
system that's because I was taking huge jumps all over this base and so here the
나는 거대한 복용했기 때문에의 시스템은 모든 그래서 여기에이 기본 이상 및 점프
loss function is minimal at the blue part there and it's high in the reports
손실 함수가 파란색 부분에 최소이며 보고서에서 높은입니다
so we want to get to them as part of the basin this is actually with the loss
그래서 우리는 분지의 일부로서 그들에게 싶어이 손실로 실제로
function looks like Princess p.m. or discretion is our complex problems so
기능은 공주 오후 모양 또는 재량 그래서 우리의 복잡한 문제입니다
it's really just a bowl and we're trying to get to the bottom of it but this bowl
정말 그냥 그릇 그리고 우리는 그것의 바닥하지만이 그릇에 도착하기 위해 노력하고
is like 30,000 dimensional so that's why takes awhile
잠시 걸리는 이유 등 30,000 차원 그래서입니다
ok so we take a step and we we evaluate the gradient and repeat this over and
확인 그래서 우리는 조치를 취할 우리는 우리가 그라데이션을 평가하고 이상이 반복
over in practice there's this additional part I wanted to mention where we don't
이상 실제로 우리가하지 않는 위치를 언급 원이 추가 부분이있다
actually evaluate the loss for the entire training did in fact all we do is
실제로 전체 훈련에 대한 손실은 우리가하는 모든 일이 실제로 한 평가
we only use what's called me back reading the st. where we have this
우리는 단지 일을 읽고 나에게 다시 전화 무엇을 사용합니다. 우리는이 곳
entire dataset but we sample batches from it so we sample sale like say
말처럼 우리는 판매를 샘플링 때문에 전체 데이터 세트는하지만 우리는 그것에서 일괄 샘플
thirty two examples out of my training data I evaluate the loss of the gradient
삼십로서는 내 트레이닝 데이터로부터 I 그래디언트의 손실을 평가할
on this batch of 32 and then I knew my primary update and I keep doing this
다음 32의이 배치에 내 차 업데이 트를 알고 나는이 일을 계속
over and over again and make sure what ends up happening is if you only sample
계속해서 또 다시하고 있는지 확인 무슨 일이 끝나는 것은 경우에만 샘플입니다
very few data points from training data then your estimate of the gradient of
다음, 트레이닝 데이터의 기울기중인 추정치 거의 데이터 포인트
course over the entire training set is kind of noisy because you're only
당신은 단지이기 때문에 전체 학습 집합을 통해 코스 종류의 잡음이
estimating based on a small subset of your data but it allows me to step more
데이터의 작은 하위 집합을 기반으로하지만 좀 더 단계 수 추정하는
so you can do more steps with approximate gradient or you can do few
그래서 당신은 대략 그라데이션 더 많은 단계를 수행하거나 몇 가지 작업을 수행 할 수 있습니다
steps with exact gradient and practice what ends up working better if used me
저를 사용하면 더 나은 작업을 끝 무엇 정확한 그라데이션과 연습 단계
back and it's much more efficient of course and it's impractical to actually
다시 그것을 훨씬 효율적 물론이고 실제로는 비실용적이다
do fullback gradient descent so come in many sizes 32 64 128 256 this is not
풀백 그라데이션 하강는 많은 크기 32 64 128 256이 아닌 오는가
usually hyper primarily worry about too much usually settled based on whatever
일반적으로 하이퍼 주로에 따라 너무 많은 보통 정착 걱정대로
fits on your GPU we're going to be talking about BP's in a bit but they
우리는 비트에서 BP의 이야기 될 것하지만하고 당신의 GPU에 맞는 사람들
have finite amount of memory say about like 6 gigabytes or talk about its good
메모리의 유한 한 양이 6기가바이트 등에 대해 말하거나 그것의 좋은 이야기
GPU and usually choose a backside such that a small me back to example spits in
GPU 일반적으로 후면을 선택 같은 날 작은 다시 예에서 뱉어 그
your memory so that's how usually that's the term and it's not a primary that
당신의 기억은 그래서 그 용어의 방법 일반적으로 그리고 그것은 기본이 아니다 그
actually matters a lot and optimization sense
실제로 많은 및 최적화 감각을 중요
and we're going to get the momentum in a bit but if you want to use momentum then
우리는 약간의 모멘텀을받을거야하지만 당신은 그 기세를 사용하려는 경우
this is just fine we always been about trying to send but momentum very common
이것은 우리가 항상 모멘텀이 매우 일반적인를 보낼 수 있지만 노력에 대해하고 괜찮아요
to do so just to give you an idea of what will this look like in practice if
그래서 그냥 할 당신이 연습하는 경우에 어떻게 보일까의 아이디어를 제공합니다
I'm running optimization overtime and i'm looking at the Los evaluated on just
나는 최적화 초과 근무를 실행하고 있는데 난 그냥 평가 로스 찾고 있어요
a small many batch of data and you can see that basically my loss goes down
작은 많은 데이터를 배치하고 당신은 기본적으로 내 손실이 아래로가는 것을 볼 수 있습니다
over time on these many batches from the training data so as an optimizing I'm
학습 데이터에서 이러한 여러 일괄 처리에 시간이 지남에 그래서 난 최적화로
going downhill now of course if I was doing pullbacks gradient descent so this
나는이 때문에 그라데이션 하강 주가 하락을하는 경우 지금은 물론 내리막 것
was not just me back a sample from the data you wouldn't expect as much noise
그냥 날 다시 데이터의 샘플 당신은 많은 소음을 기대하지 않을 것이다되지 않았습니다
you just expect this to be aligned to just goes down but because we use me
당신은 단지 우리가 저를 사용하기 때문에하지만 내려갑니다이가 정렬 될 것으로 예상
back if you get this noise in there because something about you are better
당신에 대해 뭔가 더 나은 있기 때문에 당신이이 노이즈를 얻을 다시하는 경우
than others but over time they could all go down there question
다른 사람보다하지만 시간이지나면서 그들은 모두가 질문을 아래로 갈 수있다
yes sir you're wondering about the shape of this loss function you're used to
예 선생님 당신은 당신이 사용하는이 손실 함수의 형태에 대해 궁금
maybe seeing more rapid improvement quick are these loss functions come in
어쩌면 더 빠른 개선을보고 바로 이러한 손실 함수에 와서 있습니다
different shapes sizes so it really depends it's not necessarily the case
정말 그것이 반드시 그렇지 않다 달려있다, 그래서 다른 모양은 크기
that loss function must look very sharp in the beginning although sometimes they
그 손실 함수는 처음에 있지만 때로는 매우 날카로운 봐야한다 그들이
do they have different shapes for example it also matters on your
그들은 그것은 또한 당신에 중요한 예를 들어 다른 모양을 가지고 수행
initialization if I'm careful with my initialization I would expect less of a
내 초기화 조심 해요 경우 초기화 내가 덜 기대
jump but if I initialize very incorrectly then you would expect that
점프하지만 매우 잘못 초기화하면 당신은 그 기대
that's going to be fixed very early on in the optimization we're going to get
그것은 우리가받을거야 최적화에 매우 초기에 해결 될 것
to some of those parts I think much later I also want to show you a lot of
그 부분의 일부 나중에 나는 또한 당신에게 많이 보여주고 싶은 많은 생각
the effects of learning rate on your loss function and the still learning
하여 손실 함수와 계속 학습의 학습 속도의 영향
rate is the step size basically a very high learning rates or step sizes you
속도는 기본적으로는 스텝 사이즈의 학습 속도 또는 스텝 사이즈하면 매우 높다
start rushing around in your W space and so i dont converge or you explode if you
당신의 W 공간에서 주위에 돌진 시작하고 그래서 난 수렴 해달라고 또는 당신은 당신이 경우 폭발
have a very low learning rate then you're barely doing any updates and also
당신은 거의 또한 업데이트를하고있어 다음 매우 낮은 학습 속도가
it takes a very long time to actually converge and if you have a high learning
실제로 수렴 시간이 오래 걸리고는 높은 교육이 있다면
rate sometimes you can basically get a kind of stuck in a bad position of a
요금은 때때로 당신은 기본적으로 나쁜 위치에 붙어의 종류를 얻을 수 있습니다
loss so these loss functions kind of you need to get down to the minimum so if
당신이 손실 함수의 종류 때문에 손실이 그렇다면 최소한으로 내려받을 필요
you have too much energy in your stocking too quickly when you don't have
당신이 없을 때 당신은 너무 빨리 당신의 스타킹에 너무 많은 에너지를 가지고
you don't allow your problem to kind of settle in on the smaller local minima
당신은 당신의 문제가 가지 작은 로컬 최소값에 정착하는 것을 허용하지 않습니다
your objective in general when you talk about neural networks and optimization
당신은 신경 네트워크 및 최적화에 대해 일반적으로 당신의 목표를 이야기 할 때
you'll see a lot of hand waving because that's the only way we communicate about
즉 우리가 통신 할 수있는 유일한 방법이기 때문에 당신은 손을 흔들며을 많이 볼 수 있습니다
these losses and distance so just imagine like a Big Basin of loss and
이러한 손실과 거리가 그래서 그냥 큰 손실의 분지와 같은 상상
there are these like smaller pockets of smaller loss and so if you're thrashing
당신은 탈곡하는 경우 이러한 작은 손실 등의 작은 주머니 같은있다
around and you can settle in on a smaller loss parts and converter for
주위에 당신은 작은 손실 부품 컨버터에 정착 할 수
their so that's why the learning rate so good and so you need to find the correct
그 때문에 그 이유는 학습 속도 너무 좋은 그래서 올바른을 찾을 필요
learning rate which will cause a lot of headaches and what people do most of the
속도를 배우는 것은 많은 두통의 원인과 사람들은 대부분 무엇을 할
time is sometimes you start off with a high learning rates we get some benefits
시간은 때때로 우리가 어떤 혜택을받을 높은 학습 속도로 시작된다
and then UDK it over time to start up with high and then we decadence learning
다음 높은 함께 시작하는 데 시간이 지남에 그것을 UDK 그리고, 우리는 학습 타락
read over time as we're settling in on the good solution and I also want to
우리는 좋은 해결책에 정착하고 시간이 지남에 읽고 나는 또한 원하는
point out who's going to this in much more detail but the way I'm doing the
훨씬 더 자세하게거야하지만 방법은 내가 일을 해요 누가 지적
update here which is how to use the gradient to actually modify your W
실제로 W을 수정 구배를 사용하는 방법이다 여기서 업데이트
that's called an update firmware update there are many different forms of doing
그 일을 여러 가지 형태가 업데이트 펌웨어 업데이트라고
it this is the simplest way which were
그것은이 있었다 가장 간단한 방법입니다
just STD simplest custom greeting cent but there are many formulas such as
다만 STD 간단한 사용자 지정 인사말 %가되지만, 많은 공식이있다
momentum that was already mentioned in momentum you basically imagine as you're
당신이있어 이미 모멘텀에 언급 된 모멘텀은 기본적으로 상상
doing this optimization you imagine keeping track of this blog city so as
이 최적화를 수행하면은 그래서이 블로그 도시의 트랙을 유지 상상
I'm stepping am also keeping track of my velocity so if I keep seeing a positive
나는 긍정적를보고 계속 그래서 만약 또한 내 속도의 트랙을 유지하고 스테핑 해요
reading some direction I will accumulate velocity in that direction so I don't
내가 그 방향으로 속도를 축적 몇 가지 방향을 읽고 그래서 난 몰라
need someone to go faster at the russian and so there are several from Los will
러시아에서 빨리 갈 사람이 필요하고 그래서 로스에서 몇 가지가 있습니다 것
look and shortly the class but Thomas prop Adam or commonly used so just to
보고 일반적으로 곧 클래스하지만 토마스 소품 아담 또는 그래서 그냥에 사용
show you what these look like these different choices and what they might do
이러한 서로 다른 선택의 모양을 그들이 할 수있는 것을 보여
in your loss function this is a figure from Alec so here we have a loss
당신의 손실 함수이 우리가 손실을 가지고, 그래서 여기에 알렉에서 그림입니다
function and these are low-level clerks and we start off opposition over there
기능과 이러한 낮은 수준의 점원 그리고 우리는 저기 반대를 시작
and we're trying to get to the basin and different update formulas will give you
우리는 당신을 줄 것이다 유역과 다른 업데이트 공식에 도착하기 위해 노력하고
better or worse convergence in different problems so you can see for example this
당신은 예를 들어이 서로 다른 문제에 좋든 나쁘 든 수렴을 볼 수 있도록
momentum in green it built up momentum as it went down and then it overshot and
녹색 모멘텀이 내려 갔다으로는 모멘텀을 구축 한 다음은 오버 슈팅과
then it kind of go back go back and this as UD takes forever to converge can read
다음은 가지 돌아가 다시 돌아가 UD 등이 읽을 수 수렴 영원히 소요
that's what I presented you so far as she takes forever to emerge and are
그것은 그녀가 등장하고 있습니다 영원히 걸립니다 내가 지금까지 당신을 제시 무엇
different ways of actually performing this primary up there are more or less
실제로이 차 위로가 수행하는 다른 방법은 더 많거나 적은
efficient in modernization will see much more of this I also wanted to mention at
현대화 효율적인 내가 또한에서 언급하고 싶었이 훨씬 더 볼 수 있습니다
this point as likely yes I want to go slightly into I'm to explain obviously
확률이이 점은 예 내가 분명히 설명 해요로 약간 가고 싶어
like your classification we know how to set up the problem we know that are
당신의 분류처럼 우리는 우리가 알고있는 문제를 설정하는 방법을 알고
different loss functions me know how to optimize them so we can kind of do at
다른 손실이 날 우리가 가지에서 할 수 있도록 그들을 최적화하는 방법을 알고 기능
this point across I wanted to mention that I want to give you a sense of what
I에서이 점은 내가 당신의 감각을 부여 할 것을 언급 원하는 것을
computer vision looked like before comments came about so that you have a
댓글에 대한 그래서 당신은을 가지고 오기 전에 컴퓨터 비전처럼 보였다
bit of historical perspective because we used a linear classifiers all the time
역사적 관점의 비트 우리는 선형 분류 모든 시간을 사용하기 때문에
but of course you don't usually your classic cars on the road original image
하지만 물론 당신은 도로 원본 이미지에없는 보통 클래식 자동차를 수행
because that's all you want to believe we solve the problems with it like you
즉 당신이 믿는하려는 모든 때문에 우리는 당신 같은 그것으로 문제를 해결
have to cover all the modes and so on I thought the police to do as they used to
나는 그들이에 사용 된 경찰이해야 할 생각에 모든 모드 등을 포함해야
compute all these different feature types of images and then you can view
모든 이미지의 서로 다른 기능 유형을 계산하고 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
different descriptors in different feature types and you get these
다른 기능 유형에서 다른 설명하면 다음을 얻을
statistical summaries of what the image looks like what the frequencies are like
이미지가 주파수처럼 어떤 모습의 통계 요약
and so on and then we can capitated all those into large vectors and then we put
등등, 그리고, 우리는 capitated 모든 큰 벡터에 그와 우리는 넣을 수 있습니다
those into linear classifiers
선형 분류에 그
so different feature types all of them concatenated and then that went until
까지 간 다음, 그들 모두 연결된 등 다양한 기능 유형
your classifiers that was usually the pipeline so just to give you an idea of
일반적으로 파이프 라인이었다 당신의 분류, 그래서 그냥 당신의 아이디어를 제공합니다
really what these talks were like one very simple feature type you might
정말 무슨 회담 당신이 수도 한 아주 간단한 기능 유형 같았다
imagine is just a color histogram so I go over all the pixels in the image and
나는 모든 이미지의 픽셀을 통해 갈 수 있도록 단지 컬러 히스토그램 상상
i'd in them and to say how many bands are there are different colors depending
나는 그들 거라고하고 따라 다른 색상이 얼마나 많은 밴드 대답
on the hue of the color as you can imagine this is kind of like one
당신이 상상할 수있는 색상의 색조에 종류의 일처럼
statistical summary of what's in the image is just a number of colors each
이미지에 무엇의 통계 요약 색상 각 단지 숫자입니다
been so this will become one of my teachers that I would eventually become
그래서 이것은 내가 결국 될 것입니다 선생님의 하나가 될 것입니다되었습니다
cutting with many different feature types and other kind of intimately the
다양한 기능의 유형과 친밀의 다른 종류의 절단
classifier if you think about it the linear classifier can use these features
분류는 당신이 그것에 대해 생각하면 선형 분류는 이러한 기능을 사용할 수 있습니다
to actually perform the classification because the linear classifier can like
선형 분류 좋아 할 수 있기 때문에 실제로 분류를 수행하는
or dislike seeing lots of different colors in the image with positive or
또는 양 또는과 이미지에 다른 색상을 많이보고 싫어
negative what's very common features also include things like what we call
부정적인 무엇 매우 일반적인 기능은 또한 우리가 부르는 등이 포함됩니다
610 hawk features basically these were you go in local neighborhoods in the
610 매 기능은 기본적으로 이러한 당신은 현지 지역에 이동했다
invention and you look at whether or not there are lots of different orientations
발명과는 다른 방향의 제비가 있는지 여부를보고
so are there lots of horizontal or vertical edges we make up histograms
그래서 수평 또는 수직 가장자리의 많은이 우리는 히스토그램을 구성
over that and so when you end up with just the summary of what kinds of edges
그 이상하고 그래서 당신은 가장자리의 종류 단지 요약 끝날 때
are wherein the image and you can calculate all those together there was
상기 이미지이고, 당신이 사람들은 모두 함께 있었다 계산할 수 있습니다
lots of different types of our proposed over to over the years just I'll be
수년에 걸쳐까지 제안 된 우리의 다른 유형의 많은 단지 내가있을거야
taxed on lots of different ways of measuring what kinds of things are there
측정하는 다른 방법을 많이에 과세 것들의 종류가
in the image and statistics of them and then we had these pipelines call back
이미지와 그들의 통계, 그리고, 우리는이 파이프 라인은 다시 전화했다
over to my place where you look at different points in your
내 장소를 통해 당신이 다른 점을보고 어디
you describe a little local patch with something that you come up with like
당신은 같은 당신이 와서 뭔가 조금 로컬 패치를 설명
looking at the frequencies are looking at the colors or whatever and then we
주파수보고는 색상을보고 또는 다음 무엇이든되고 우리
came up with these dictionaries for ok here's the stuff we're seeing images
여기에 확인 이러한 사전 내놓았다 우리가 이미지를 볼 수있는 물건입니다
like there's lots of high-frequency stop for low-frequency stuff in blue and so
같은 파란색과 낮은 주파수 물건에 대한 고주파 정지 많이있다
on
...에
to end up with the centroids using k-means of what kind of stuff to be seen
물건의 종류를 볼 수 무엇의 K-수단을 사용하여 무게 중심으로 끝낼 수 있습니다
in a just and then we express every single image as statistics over how much
A의 바로 다음 우리는 얼마 동안 통계 등의 모든 하나의 이미지를 표현
of each thing we see in the image so for example this image has lots of
예를 들어,이 이미지는 많이있다, 그래서 각각의 일의 우리는 이미지 참조
high-frequency green stuff so you might see some feature vector that basically
고주파 녹색 물건 당신은 기본적으로 몇 가지 특징 벡터가 표시 될 수 있도록
will have a higher value and high frequency and green and then we did is
더 높은 가치와 높은 주파수와 녹색이있을 것이다, 그리고, 우리는 않았다
we basically took these feature vectors
우리는 기본적으로 이러한 특징 벡터했다
needed them and put a linear classifier on them so really the context for what
그들에게 필요한 무엇을 위해 이렇게 정말 그들에 컨텍스트를 선형 분류를 넣어
we're doing is as follows what it looked like mostly computer vision before
그 이전에 대부분 컴퓨터 비전 속에서 다음과 같이 우리는 일을하는지
roughly 2012 will let you take your image and you have a step of feature
약 2012 당신이 당신의 이미지를 촬영하게되며 기능의 단계를
extraction where we decided what are important things to you know about an
추출 우리는 당신이에 대해 알아야 할 중요한 일이 무엇인지 결정 곳
image different frequencies different tents and we decided on what are
이미지 서로 다른 주파수 다른 텐트와 우리는 어떤 결정
interesting features and you see people take like 10 different feature types in
흥미로운 기능은 당신이 사람들이 10 개의 서로 다른 기능 유형처럼 걸릴 참조
every paper and just woke up need all of it just hit you can double one giant
모든 종이와 그냥 일어 났는데 그냥 당신이 하나의 거대한 두 배로 할 수 있습니다 히트 그것의 모든 필요
feature vector over your image and then you put a linear classifier on top of it
기능 이미지를 통해 벡터 및 당신은 그 위에 선형 분류를 넣어
just like we saw it right now and so you play a train sale in your ass p.m. on
우리는 지금 그것을보고처럼 그래서 당신은에 당신의 엉덩이 오후에 기차 판매를 재생
top of all these feature types and what we're replacing it since then we found
이러한 모든 기능 유형의 상단과 우리가 우리가 발견 한 이후로 교체하고
that works much better as you start with the raw image and you think of the whole
그건 당신이 원시 이미지로 시작하는만큼 더 잘 작동하고 전체의 생각
thing you're not designing some part of it in isolation of what you think is a
당신이 생각하는 어떤 것은 당신의 분리에의 일부를 설계하지 않는
good idea or not we come up with an architecture that can simulate a lot of
많은 시뮬레이션 할 수 있습니다 우리가 건축을 마련 좋은 아이디어 나하지
different features so to speak and since everything is just a single function we
모든 것이 하나의 기능 우리 때문에 다른 특징은 그렇게 말하고합니다
don't just trying to top it on top of the features of we can actually train
단지 우리가 실제로 훈련 할 수의 기능의 상단에 상단하려고하지 않는다
all the way down to the pixels and we can train our feature extractors
모든 방법 화소에 이르기까지 우리는 우리의 기능 추출기를 훈련 할 수있다
effectively so that was a big innovation and how you approach this problem is we
효과적으로 있도록 큰 혁신이었다 당신이 접근 방법이 문제는 우리는
try to eliminate a lot of hand engineered components are trying to have
반면 설계 요소를 많이 가지고하려고하는 제거 시도
a single the principal blob so that we can fully trained to pull things
우리가 완벽하게 일을 끌어 훈련을 할 수 있도록 하나의 주요 얼룩
starting at the Rock Texas that's what historically this is coming from and
역사적으로이 오는하고 무엇을 그 바위 텍사스에서 시작
what we will be doing and so next last will be looking specifically at this
우리는 무엇을하고있을 것입니다 그래서 다음 마지막이에 구체적으로보고됩니다
problem of we need to compute analytic gradients and so we're going to go into
우리의 문제는 분석 구배를 계산해야하고 그래서 우리는에 갈거야
backpropagation which is an efficient way of computing analytics gradient and
분석 기울기를 계산하는 효율적인 방법은 역 전파 및
so that's backdrop and you're going to become good at it and then we're going
그래서 그 배경 그리고 당신은 잘 될거야 그리고 우리는거야
to go slightly works
약간 작동 이동